你買了這啊 是啊
You bought this? Yeah.
現在是我們的了 額哼
And it's ours now. We own this. Mm-hmm.
我愛上這裡了 是的吧
I love it. Right?
我就跟你說嘛 你看這個內嵌式的壁爐
What'd I tell you? The fireplace, the built-ins here.
你確定就給你姐妹這個嗎
Are you sure you want to give this to your sister?
寶貝 我們花了一整天跑了百公裡過來啊
Babe, we'd make 100K off this flip all day long.
花心思整理一下唄 就這兒嗎
Trying to make up... This is it?
啊 是的 進來吧 你倆叫我早來一個鐘頭就為了
Hey, yeah. Come in. You guys made me ask off an hour early to see
這個垃圾場嗎
this dump?
我們都深有感受不是麼 是啊 感覺就像
We're all smelling this, right? Yeah, it smells like I'm
我在呼吸新鮮的排泄物
breathing piss.
沒錯 不是個好地方 我們趕緊走
Okay. Not a good fit. So we'll just go.
走吧 拜托 再看看嘛
Come on. Come on. Have a little vision.
看看這法式木門 通向花園
French doors to the garden.
我們移走這些椅子 打掉這些
We move the stairs, take these walls down,
搞個通向廚房的開放空間
create an open concept through the kitchen.
看看這角落裡華麗的染色玻璃 看這結構
There's a gorgeous stained glass here in the corner. The bones are
真棒
really good.
那我們何時拿出12000美元來修這個爛掉的地基
When's the part we cough up 12 grand to fix the rotted-out foundation?
很明顯這些只能搞定一部分 El
Clearly, it's not for them. Let's just flip this one, El.
穿過這條街就有一座公園
There's a park across the street.
將來你們有了孩子這還有座學校
And the schools here are fantastic if you have a baby.
不好意思 什麼時候 吉米
When. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Kimmy.
什麼時候要孩子啊
When. When you have a baby.
我們就要有孩子了 我們的確有了
We're having a baby. We are having a baby.
你知道嗎 這叫宇宙的顯現
You see that? That's called manifesting to the universe.
有時候 宇宙會覺得我把這26000塊拿到外面先扔了
Sometimes the universe thinks it's funny if I drop $26,000 on in
會比較有趣
vitro first.
哈 你真壞 我就開個玩笑
Oh! You're a dick. I'm kidding.
如果這裡真這麼棒 你們怎麼不搬來
If this place is so great, why don't you guys move in here?
那讓他們怎麼面對五個臥室和一座公園呢
What are they gonna do with five bedrooms and a park?
很顯然他們不會有寶寶
They're obviously never having kids.
看看 他們可沒有什麼情感漏洞要填補
Look at 'em. They don't have any emotional holes to fill.
現在我們可要補上
Not that we are doing it to fill...
別說了 Russ 好的
Shut up, Russ. All right.
干嘛這樣看著我 我怎麼了
What was that look? What look?
他剛才說你們不會有孩子 然後你
He just said you guys were never gonna have kids. Then you did a
很明顯是在看我
definite look.
是啊 你什麼眼神 你後來回頭
Yeah, what was the look for? You looked back at me to include me in
看著我
your look.
我沒看啊 絕對看了
I didn't do a look. Totally did a look.
沒有 我想我們正在制造一些麻煩
It wasn't a look. I think we just started some trouble.
能有什麼麻煩 甚至可能要打起來咯
There's no trouble. Maybe even a fight.
不會打起來的 沒有任何麻煩 我們走吧
There's no fight. There's no trouble. Let's get out of here.
天哪 你們不會是要孩子了吧
Oh, my God. You guys are gonna have kids now, aren't you?
沒啊 Kimmy 我不明白 你說什麼
No. What? Kimmy. I don't know. What?
你當然有了 因為你無論如何都要贏我
Of course you are, because you have to win at everything.
然後你還要拿你完美的子宮打我臉吧
Then you're gonna throw your perfect uterus in my face too.
你怎麼知道我的子宮很完美 我們甚至沒有嘗試
How do you know my uterus is perfect? We've never even tried to have
要小孩
kids.
我都不清楚我是否能懷孕
I don't know if I can get pregnant.
當然很完美咯 因為是你的嘛
Of course it is perfect. It is yours.
嘿吉米 可能還有皮革內飾呢
Kimmy. It probably has a leather interior.
別走 吉米 你才剛來呢
Please, Kimmy. You just got here.
對不起了 彼得 加油吧
Sorry, Petey. Have a good fight.
下次見 拉斯
See you later, Russ.
我沒給臉色 你現在就有
I didn't do a look. You're doing a look right now.
並沒有 你才是在給臉色
There's no look. You're doing a look.
好吧 可能我是給了臉色
All right, maybe I did do a look.
但是聽到他好大聲地說 我們不會有小孩
But just hearing him say it out loud: "We're never having children."
我意思是 真的嗎
I mean, is that true?
我不提這事就是因為每次我說時候你都講
I quit bringing it up because every time I did, you'd say it's not
不是時候
the right time.
我明白 但我們總是配合不到一起
I know, but we were always so broke.
之後我們又變得瘋狂 想要重新開始這事
And then we were going crazy trying to get the business started.
我們今年已經看了五套房了 我想開始漸漸放下
We've flipped five houses this year, and I'm starting to turn down
設計的工作
design work.
我總是在想我有一天會當媽媽
I always thought that I'd be a mom someday.
我想我準備好了 真棒 你現在又說準備好了
I think I'm ready. Great. Now you're ready.
然後到孩子十六歲 我就是老齡父親了
And by the time the kid's 16, I'm gonna be one of those old dads,
就像布萊恩 亨德裡克森他爸
like Brian Hendrickson's dad.
嘿 爸 怎麼樣啊 兒子
Hey, Dad. What's up, Son?
嘿 亨德裡克森先生 長傳
Hey, Mr. Hendrickson, go long!
爸
Dad?
你殺死了我老爸
You killed my dad!
嘿 爸 醒醒啊
Hey. Hey, Dad. Wake up, wake up. Wake up!
你可沒害死亨德裡克森桑
You did not kill Mr. Hendrickson.
而且你沒那麼老
And you're not that old.
我有個點子 如果我們收養個五歲的小孩呢
Here's an idea. What if we adopt a five-year-old?
那我36歲也能大干一場 如何
It'd be like I got cracking when I was 36. How about that?
保持直線結束可以嗎
Keep your end straight, will you?
兄弟 你想多了 沒哪個要孩子是計劃好了的
Look, you're overthinking it, bro. None of my kids were planned.
想要孩子了 你搞定它 就這麼簡單
Kid shows up, you figure it out. Easy-peasy.
你現在有幾個孩子了 斯圖 第四個快要
How many kids you got now, Stu? Number four's in the oven right
出生了
Now.
喔哦 對付孩子沒什麼難的
Wow. Nothing hard about kids.
只要你為他們花時間 他們就很乖
As long as you spend some time with them, they're cool.
最重要的是和孩子他媽能和睦共處
Most important thing, make sure the moms all get along.
嘿 肉球
Meatball. Hey! Hey, buddy!
想我了嗎
Hey. You miss me?
哦 乖孩子 想我了是吧 我也想你
Oh! That's my boy. You missed me, huh? I missed you too.
真乖
Yeah. You're such a good boy.
嘿 艾莉 我弄來了廚房用的毛巾樣品
Hey, El. I got the towel samples you wanted for the kitchen.
艾莉 你還好嗎
El, you okay?
嘿 怎麼了
Hey, what's the matter?
沒什麼 我就在想你說的領養一個
Nothing. I was just thinking about what you said about adopting a
五歲小孩
Five-year-old.
我有這麼說過嗎 是啊
I said that? Yeah.
我就是開個玩笑 我知道 是有點瘋狂
I was totally... I was joking. I know. It's kind of crazy.
但我真的想了想 寄養中心真的有很多小孩
But it just got me thinking. And there's so many kids in foster care.
而且他們經常搬來搬去 沒有任何親人
And they're moving from place to place, and they don't have anybody,
這是最讓我難過的
and it's like the saddest thing I've ever seen.
我找到了這個領養機構 下周他們有個介紹會
I found this adoption agency. They're having an orientation next week.
別給我看這個 我不想看到他們的小臉
No, don't show me that. I don't want to see those little faces.
你想傷我心嗎 我才剛工作回來呢
You trying to break my heart? I just got home from work.
艾莉 照顧這些小孩的是一些很特別的人
Ellie, people who take in foster kids are really special.
都是些志願者 甚至沒有
These are the kind of people who volunteer when it's not even a
假期
Holiday.
我們可沒有假期做志願者
We don't even volunteer on a holiday.
如果有些 嗯 殘疾的呢
What if there was, like, a disaster?
那可就像臟彈 那都無所謂
What, like a dirty bomb? Whatever.
還有那些孩子都到我們家門口了
And there's a little kid who ends up on our doorstep.
我們就要趕走他們 只因為我們不夠特殊嗎
Are we gonna turn her away because we're not special enough?
那就取決於 那要考慮很多因素的
That would depend. There's a lot of factors that go into it.
我是說 我們的食物配給以及可接受的範圍
I mean, our food rations, the blast radius.
艾莉 你不能在意我隨便說的話
El, you can't take some offhanded remark I made
然後做出個瘋狂地決定
and turn it into a crazy life decision.
那就是一句玩笑
It was a joke.
是啊
Yeah.
我明白 我只是
I know. I just...
你是對的 不能逼你去做
You're right. You shouldn't be pushed into something you don't want
你不想做的
to do.
那確實是個好想法
It was just a nice thought.
晚安
Good night.
好的 我不會再開那些玩笑了
All right, I won't make any more jokes like that.
行嗎
All right?
你想看些待修房嗎
You wanna watch a little Fixer Upper?
好吧 我愛你 我也愛你
Okay, I love you. I love you.
我很空虛 我的盆友
That's a long fill-up, my friend.
那就是為什麼我想你來
Well, that's because I wanted you to come in here.
我們來場空手道對決吧 就我跟你 一對一
We're gonna have a karate kicking contest. Me versus you, straight up.
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
這不公平 這真的
It's not fair. That is not...
嘿
Hey.
你可不能再買這些薯片了 太辣了
You can't buy these pita chips anymore. They're way too spicy.
辣的我要流鼻涕了
I'm getting my nose watery and...
現在有超過五十萬的寄養兒童
Over a half million children are currently in foster care.
系統超載了 知道嗎
The system is overloaded, okay?
不能再接收更多孩子了
It doesn't need any more kids.
因此 孩子必須得轉移 而且生活條件更差
So for a child to be removed, conditions have to be pretty bleak,
通常包括虐待或者被極端忽視
usually involving abuse or extreme neglect.
他們中的一些更是變得憔悴
And some of these kids can often languish in the system,
除非有更多像你們這樣優質家庭的參與
unless a wonderful family like yours steps up for them.
我們一定參與 我們現在就要帶走一個
We'll step up. We'll take one right away.
好極了 我們現在就去登記 看看我們的存貨
Perfect. Let me go check in back, see what we have in stock.
她當然是在開玩笑
She is kidding, of course.
我們可沒有庫存
We do not stock.
你們懂的
And you know that.
我們可以帶你們學習八周的收養家庭課程
But we can take you through the eight-week foster parenting course,
然後你們就會得到資格證
and you can get your certification.
然後我們就會幫你們與一些寄養孩子配對
And then we can pair you with some kids that you can foster
直到你們領養成功
until they become adoptable.
但這可不簡單哦 大伙兒
But it is not gonna be easy, folks.
這些孩子會測試你們的意願
These kids will test your will,
給你們的關系制造壓力
put a strain on your relationship,
一不留神就會被淘汰
and push buttons you didn't even know you had.
我敢當你們面說並不是所有人都能做到
I can tell by looking at you that not all y'all are gonna make it.
事實上我想你們應該有勇氣面對這些不快
I actually think this group has got the grit to face some unpleasant..
打擾一下 你們這就走啦
Excuse me. Y-You guys heading out?
是 好吧 謝謝 再見
Yeah. Okay. Well, thank you. Bye-bye.
好吧 怪我 很明顯是的
All right, that one's on me. It absolutely is.
我們之前也有過類似經歷 是的
We've gone over this before. We have.
是個問題 沒錯
This is a problem. It's a problem.
好的 各位 不如我們來了解下你們的名字
Okay, everybody, why don't we learn your names
以及你們中意那種類型的孩子
and what type of children you're looking for.
哦 你好
Oh, hi.
我們是戴安娜 和 迪克 麥坎
We're Dana and Dirk McCann.
是上帝指引我們來這
And the Lord has guided us here
來收養一個小男孩 女孩也行
to adopt a baby boy... or a girl.
是的 上帝一直在保佑我們 嗯哼
Yeah, the big guy, he's blessed us with so much. Mm-hmm.
我們就想與孩子分享一個家 是的
We'd just like to share it with a child that needs a home. Yeah.
你們呢
What about over here?
我是大衛 這是我妻子傑西
I'm David, and this is my wife, Jessie.
我們為了孩子已經努力三年了
And we've been trying to have a baby for three years now.
但不管我們怎麼做 我就是不能懷上
But no matter what we do, I... I can't...
不好意思 能直接輪到下一位嗎 沒關系
I'm sorry. Can someone else go? It's okay.
好的 我是基特 這是邁克爾
It's okay. Well, I'm Kit and this is Michael.
我們也在努力要孩子
We've also been trying to conceive now.
大概從我們第一次見面開始 對吧
Pretty much since the first night we met, right?
沒錯 我們只是不太走運
That is correct. We're just not having any luck.
我們想收養一個9歲左右的孩子
We're looking for a child of any gender
不論性別種族
or ethnicity up to nine years old.
你們好 我是十月 羅斯詹妮斯
Hello. My name is October Ross Jennings.
我想做個單親母親收養一個
And I would like to be the single mother
有運動天賦的青少年
of an athletically gifted teen boy
我能激發他獲得全一級獎學金的潛力
who I can help to reach his full Division One scholarship potential.
最好是美非混血
Preferably African-American.
嗯哼 好的
Mm-hmm. Right?
就像電影 弱點 是嗎 真棒
Like The Blind Side. Like the movie. Right? That's great.
親愛的 她不是在開玩笑
Honey, she's not joking.
你是在開玩笑嗎 天哪 對不起
A-Are you jo... You're not joking? My God. I'm so sorry.
我以為還在跟著那倆基佬的懷孕梗開玩笑呢
I just thought 'cause of the gay guys' conceiving joke that we were...
我意思是 這是電影 弱點 的劇情啊
I mean, that is the plot of The Blind Side, so...
我沒看過 所以 拜托 到你了
I've never seen it. So, please, it's your turn. Just do not talk to
別再說我了
me anymore.
嗯 她發飆了
Yeah, she's nuts.
對不起 我感覺很糟
I'm so sorry. I feel terrible. I, uh...
我叫Ellie 你們好 這是我老公Pete
So, my name's Ellie. Hi. This is my husband, Pete.
額 是的 我意思是我還不是很了解這個
Uh, yeah, I mean, I'm not too sure about any of this.
我是說 我明白 我們收養了一只狗 我們愛它到
I mean, I get it. We adopted our dog Meatball, and we love him like
發狂 但
crazy, but...
別拿孩子跟狗比 我沒有啊
Don't compare kids to dogs. I'm not.
我只是說過去從動物收容所領養狗是一種
I'm just saying there used to be a stigma about getting a dog from
恥辱
the pound,
現在稱作拯救狗狗 而且每個人都想要一個
but now they're called rescue dogs and everybody wants one.
別再說 收容所 狗狗 了
Don't say "pound," don't say "dog." Just don't.
好的  這並不是
Okay, no, that's not...
只是有點小擔心對吧
It's just all of this is a little scary, right?
可能你們稱其為拯救孩子 哦 天哪
But maybe if you call them rescue kids... Oh, my God.
來代替收養 這讓更多人能容易接受
...instead of foster kids, more people would be into it
這樣人們就不會在你的研討會中途離開
and people wouldn't walk out in the middle of your seminar
這對你們的項目更有幫助 彼得別
and it'd be good for your program. Pete! Pete!
我只是說 別說了
I'm just saying... Just stop it!
看吶 各位 這是今天的演講嘉賓
Oh, everyone, our guest speaker of the day,
布蘭達費爾南德斯和他的家人
Brenda Fernandez and her parents.
讓他們感受你們的熱情吧
Let's make them feel welcome.
嘿 謝謝
Hey, thank you.
你們好
Hi.
當我八歲時
So, when I was eight years old,
我媽和她男朋友決定
my mom and her boyfriend decided it would be a good idea
在我們的車庫建一座制毒工廠
to build a meth lab in our garage.
他們逼我為他們販毒
They made me deliver drugs for them.
他們虐待我 有些客人也會
They abused me physically, and some of their customers abused me
對我實施性虐待
sexually.
我十一歲時 我們的車庫炸了
Uh, when I was 11, our garage exploded,
然後我就到這來了
and I was put in the system,
從一個地方到另一個地方
bounced around from placement to placement.
很快我就十四了
Pretty soon I was 14.
沒人想要個十幾歲的少年 過幾年更大了
Nobody wants a teenager, so I'd be aging out in a few years.
事實就是一般的孩子都超過了收養年齡
The thing is, over half the kids who age out of foster care
最終就是無家可歸 染毒 或者沒兩年就死了
end up homeless, addicted, incarcerated, or dead within two years.
輪到我了 我嘗試開始我作為成年人的生活
That was gonna be me, trying to start my adult life,
但沒有家庭願意資助我上大學
but with no family to help me pick a college,
節假日也無家可回
nobody to come home to on the holidays
為第一任男友劈腿而哭泣
or cry to when my first boyfriend dumped me for Missy Howard.
但這兩位 非常特別的人出現了
But then those two... very special people came along.
而我並沒有和善的對待他們
And I didn't make it easy on them.
但無論我如何趕他們走
But no matter how hard I pushed them away,
他們總是帶來午飯並帶我兜風
they were always there with a sack lunch and a ride.
謝謝你們
Thanks, you guys.
到這來爸爸 還有你媽媽
Come here, Daddy. You too, Mama.
真棒
That was good.
我為之前關於 弱點 的不當言論道歉
I am so sorry about the Blind Side comment.
我愛這部電影
I love the movie.
再見 布蘭達 干得不錯 很棒 好的 基特 再見
Bye, Brenda. Great job. Amazing. All right, Kit, bye.
德克 課上再見 大伙兒再見
Dirk. We'll see you in the classes, buddy. Bye, guys. Hey.
如今 你覺得我們足夠特殊嗎 可能吧
So now you think we're special enough? Maybe we are.
我是說 這就是我們要做的
I mean, this is what we do.
我們看到事情的潛在因素 搞定它 就像他們
We see potential in things, we fix 'em up. Like they did.
他們在這孩子 年久失修 的狀態中找到她
They find this kid in a state of disrepair,
給她漆上新漆 刮去情感屋頂的
they give her a new coat of paint, scrape off her emotional popcorn
無用紋理
ceiling,
安裝上愛與自尊的工作臺
install some countertops in the form of love or self-esteem, whatever.
我並不是說她像一個房子 就如我形容狗
I'm not saying she's a house like the way I said the dog thing in
那樣
there,
但我想我們會很適合做這樣的事
but I think we're perfect for this.
但她真的 他不是一幢房子 彼得
But she's really... she's not a house, Pete.
我說了她不是房子 你在聽我說嗎 當然
I just said she's not a house. Are you listening to me? Okay. No,
當然在聽
I am.
我很興奮 你呢
I'm so exci... Are you excited?
我就是有點擔心
I just get worried
事情真的會跟你想的那樣簡單嗎
that you think things are gonna be easier than they actually are.
什麼 我沒說啊 你說了
What? I do not. You do.
整件事都是你的想法啊 我現在嗨到不行
This whole thing was your idea. Now I'm pumped about it, and you're
而你卻不激動
not?
不不 我有嗨到 是嗎 看起來可不像
No, no, I am pumped. Well, you don't look pumped.
面對這樣一個改變你生活的重要時刻 你應該表現得更嗨
A big, life-altering moment like this, you gotta get pumped.
我倆可是要去干件瘋狂的大事呢
We're about to do something insane.
你有聽她說什麼嗎 當然
Did you hear her speak? Yes.
那是我這輩子聽到的最贊的 我知道哦
It was the greatest thing I've ever heard. I know.
來吧 女牛仔 跟著我說
Come on, cowgirl, let me get a "yee-haw." Yee-haw.
不是這樣  跟我學  咦哈
No, bull. Gimme one. Yee-haw!
大聲點  瘋狂點  快點  你都快要成為一個媽媽了
Louder. Crazier. Come on. Come on! You're about to be a mom!
咦哈
Yaaa-hoo!
填個氣球  艾爾
Add a balloon, El.
好的  坐下吧
Okay, have a seat.
時間到了
Time's up.
這些是你幻想中的孩子
These are your fantasy kids.
不是你真正的孩子
They are not your real children.
加油  傑西  你快失去她了
Come on, Jessie. You're losing her.
彼得 彼得 彼得  滴答滴答  肌肉男
Pete. Pete, Pete! Ticktock, muscle man.
這還不能夠讓你從喂給他的花生醬中
That's not gonna bring him back from that peanut butter sandwich you
救回他
fed him.
你真正的孩子會非常不一樣  不能擦除他們的
Your real kids will be very different. Can't erase 'em.
做的很好  邁克爾
Good job, Michael.
好了  十月
All right, October.
我宣布  你的孩子去世了
I'm calling it. Yours is dead.
都在這了嗎
All there?
是時候把這些想法抹除了
Time to erase these ideals right now.
馬上就好
Almost done.
馬上就好了  好的  好的
Almost done. Okay. Okay.
謝謝你
Thank you. Thank you.
好了  所有人  我想讓你們設想一下
All right, everybody, I want you all to imagine
(恭喜你們這些被鑒證出的繼父繼母)
你得到了一個新的舒服的工作
you got this plush new job.
他們給你一個又大又好的辦公室
They give you a nice big office.
有健身房和冷凍酸奶機就在
There's a gym and a frozen yogurt machine right there in the break
休息室
room.
我愛極了冷凍酸奶
I love frozen yogurt.
但是內心深處  你知道自己不夠資格
But deep down, you know you're not qualified.
你心裡深知
In your heart of hearts,
你自己還不夠好  以後會被開除
you know you're not good enough and you are going to get fired.
就像你之前三次被開除一樣
The same way you got fired from your last three jobs.
你也有可能主動辭職去拿回一些掌控權
And you might quit just to get some control back.
你甚至有可能打翻那該死的冷凍酸奶機
Hell, you might even tip over that damn yogurt machine
然後不要臉的從那裡走出去
and walk your ass right on out of there.
澄清一下
Just to clarify,
凱倫不是在倡導在工作的地方搞破壞
Karen is not advocating vandalism in the workplace.
重點在於  內心感受是一樣的
The point is, that it's the same...
對於一個被冷落的孩子來說
for a displaced child...
他知道你其實並不想要他
who knows... that you don't want her.
除了為失去工作
Except instead of grieving...
而悲傷
the loss of a job,
她在失去和所有人和事
she's losing her connection
的聯系
with everything and everyone.
但仍有一個聯系
But the one connection
還存在
that can remain
就是同胞兄妹之間的聯系
is between siblings.
有時對於同胞兄妹來說更容易去適應
Sometimes it's easier for sibs to adjust
因為他們不是孤獨一個人的經歷了生活中的一切
because they're not going through it all alone.
你也許會考慮去升級到同胞兄妹的級別
You might want to consider upgrading to a sibling set.
德克  你會考慮同胞兄妹嗎
Dirk? Would you consider siblings?
這大家伙也許會笑出來
The big guy might smile on that.
我們要去
Um, w-we'd have to...
我們要去祈禱  對  親愛的  沒錯
We'd pray on that. Right, honey. Yeah.
去祈禱  那大家伙不會給你超過你所能
Pray on it. The big guy wouldn't give you any more than you can
掌控的
handle.
我不敢茍同
I beg to differ.
彼得  艾利  你好啊
Pete. Ellie. Hey.
你來了  你好
You made it. Hi.
來簽個到  然後帶著這個表格
Just sign in, and take this form with you
寫下任何你見到的你可能感興趣的孩子的名字
and write down the name of any kid you meet you might be interested
字幕
in.
真的嗎  就是這麼做的嗎
Really? That's how this works?
沒錯  這是有點像購買孩子
Yeah, it can feel a little like shopping for kids.
這有些混亂  我知道  但是國家弄了這些
It's messed up, I know, but the county puts these on
因為他們能快速的配對到很多孩子和父母
because they can match a lot of kids and parents quickly.
天吶  看看那邊的大孩子
God, look at the big kids over there.
我心都碎了
Breaks my heart.
大多數人對青少年不感興趣
Most folks want nothing to do with teenagers.
當然  除非你們兩個認為你們可以給大點的孩子讓出地方
Of course, if you two thought you could make room for an older child..
不  我的意思是  我  天啊
Um, I mean... I... Oh, God.
對不起  都是我們的不好  對不起
I'm so sor... We... We're terrible people. I'm sorry.
不是你們的錯  現在進去吧  給自己找個家  去吧
You're not terrible. Now get on in there and find you a family. Go on.
天啊  這感覺好奇怪
God, it's so weird.
正常情況下  你走出去  和公園內的任意一個孩子聊聊天
Normally, you go out and chat up some random kid in a park and you're
你會被逮捕的
gonna get arrested.
我們現在就應該這麼做嗎  我明白你的想法
Now we're just supposed to? I know.
這個小家伙就他自己一個人待著  想去打個招呼嗎
This little guy's all by himself. You want to go say hi?
是的  沒錯
Yeah. Okay.
打擾一下  對不起  非常抱歉  此孩被占  等下  對不起
Excuse me. Sorry. So sorry. Occupied. Hey! Sorry.
被我們占了  不好意思
Occupied! Sorry!
我們只是去買點東西  你們讓開點  行嗎
We just went to get treats. So, yeah, just back it up. Okay?
看啊  我們帶來了點零食  來  盧卡斯  來這邊
Hey, look, we got some snacks. Come on, Lucas, right over here.
打擾一下  注意
Hey. Excuse me! Heads up!
沒事了  謝謝
Never mind. Thanks.
你拿住它  然後嘗試把它扔到他嘴裡
You just take it and try to throw it into his mouth.
真的  你想來試一下嗎
Really. You want to have a go?
好吧
Oh.
很高興見到你
Nice to meet you.
抓到了嗎  很好  把她帶過來
Get it? Oh, yeah. Bring her in!
等下  你要等著輪到你  兄弟
Hey. You gotta wait for your turn, buddy.
很抱歉  沒事  讓我們去別的地方吧
I'm sorry. Let's... Let's just go. Let's just go.
彼得  艾莉
Pete. Ellie.
最近怎麼樣  你好
How's it going? Hey.
還好吧  這一點奇怪
Yeah, well... it's a little weird.
是的  這些事情是有點尷尬
Yeah, these things can be kind of awkward.
但是你們遇見任何感興趣的孩子了嗎
But did you meet any kids that you're curious about?
我們碰見一個自己一個人坐著的小女孩
We met one little girl who was sitting all by herself.
很可愛  有點內向  好像在周圍豎起了隔離
Very sweet, a little guarded. Kind of had a little wall around her.
對於同齡人來說她也很矮小  有可能是懷胎時飲酒或者
Really small for her age too. Maybe a fetal alcohol thing or
別的什麼原因
something.
我看見她  就在那邊
I saw her... Oh, right there.
那個有悲傷臉的扎著辮子的小女孩
The little sad-looking one with pigtails
看起來像是大半輩子被一個散熱器束縛了
who seems like she's been chained to a radiator half her life.
呃  那是我女兒  那個散熱器孩子嗎
Uh, that's my daughter. The radiator kid?
什麼
What?
是的  那是我女兒
Yeah. That's my daughter.
不好意思
I'm so sorry.
你不必抱歉  我很為她驕傲
You don't have to be sorry. I'm really proud of her.
她不和別人坐一起的原因是因為她有了一個家庭
The reason she's sitting away from others is because she has a family,
一個很幸福的家庭
a very happy family.
而且我懷孕的時候也沒碰一滴酒  我也沒有一個
And I didn't drink a drop when I was pregnant. Nor do I have a
散熱器
radiator.
當然  你應該感到驕傲  我是的
Of course. You should be really proud. I am.
我受不了看著那些了  不管了  我要去那邊了
I'm sick of looking at that. To hell with it. I'm going over there.
彼得  等下  彼得
Pete. Hey, Pete.
彼得  你在做什麼  去那邊看看他們
Pete, what are you doing? Look at them over there.
他們就像粘過屎一樣  所有人都避開他們  我只是想
Everybody's avoiding them like they're dipped in shit. I'm just gonna
去打個招呼
go say hi.
好吧  等下  彼得  等一下
Yeah, okay... Hey, Pete, Pete, just wait.
我知道  我感覺這很糟糕  但是他們是青少年  明白嗎
I know. I think it's awful. But they're teenagers, okay?
他們吸毒  他們還打飛機
They use drugs, and they masturbate,
他們還在油管網站上看別人玩電子游戲
and they watch people playing video games on YouTube.
我們還沒為那些做好準備  那我們應該為什麼做好準備
We're not equipped for that. What do we have to be equipped for?
我只是想去打個招呼  我知道  我不認為我們應該那麼做
I'm just going to say hello. I know. I don't think we should do that.
打擾一下  你好  你好
Excuse me? Hi. Hey. Hi.
你好啊
Hi!
只是想告訴你一下  我們都能聽見的
Just FYI, we can all hear you.
什麼  粘過屎
Hmm? "Dipped in shit."
打飛機  這些話
"Masturbate," so forth.
我們很感謝這些關心  但沒必要說的這麼
Uh, we appreciate the concern, but there's no need to go all pity
瘋狂
crazy.
我們知道這是怎麼來的
We know how this works.
去別的地方吧  沒事的
So just go on. It's okay.
去和那些小孩子混在一起  不要多想  好嗎
Go mingle with the kiddies and don't give it another thought, okay?
過得愉快  謝謝  再見
Have a good day, folks. Thanks. Bye-bye.
那麼  你們兩個出去  還是給自己找了個青少年
So, you two went out and found yourself a teenager after all, huh?
我們只見了幾秒鐘  但是她留下了一個很好的印像
We only met her for a second. But she made a real impression.
是的  麗茲是一個很好的孩子
Oh, yeah. Lizzy's such a great kid.
她在學校表現很好  來這邊
She does really well in school. Come on back.
四年前她十一歲的時候就來照顧所了
She came into care four years ago when she was 11.
花了很久去勸說她接受安置在一個寄養家庭
Took a lot to convince her to accept placement in an adoptive home.
她媽媽  把房子弄起火了  在裂掉的管子旁暈倒了
Her mother... Set the house on fire, passed out with a crack pipe.
我想說的是  在我說出事實之前
What I was gonna say... Before I told it like it is?
在你打斷我之前
Before you jumped on in there,
她媽媽這幾年來許下了很多承諾
is that her mother's made a lot of promises over the years
但從來沒有將它們進行到底
and never seems to follow through with them.
她媽媽現在在哪裡
Where's her mom now?
也許在院子裡穿著連衣褲賣著香煙
Probably in an orange jumpsuit selling smokes in the yard.
我保證那並不準確
I'm sure that's not accurate.
最後發現麗茲的媽媽就在監獄裡接受判決
Huh. Turns out Lizzy's mom is finishing a sentence in county jail.
誰說過什麼  誰說過
Who called it, huh? Who said it?
你說過  好吧
You did. Yeah.
看起來她沒有來和她的孩子重聚
Looks like she's never pursued reunification
也在超過兩年內沒有聯系過她的孩子
or contacted her kids in over two years,
那麼  好吧  她差不多就是無足輕重的事
so, yeah, she's pretty much a nonissue.
這糟糕極了  那她爸爸呢
That's terrible. What about the father?
你在說什麼呢  爸爸
What are you talking about, "father"?
你在給我們表演喜劇嗎  彼得
What, are you doing comedy for us now, Pete?
凱倫  我們有很多站出來的爸爸
Karen, we've had plenty of fathers who have stepped up,
但是在這裡  任何生父都沒有名字
but in this case, no ID's on any birth fathers.
聽著  麗茲的媽媽是體系下的產物
Look, Lizzy's mom is a product of the system
她沒學過怎麼照顧好自己  更不要說三個
and she never learned to properly care for herself, much less three
孩子了
kids.
三個  三個孩子嗎  什麼
Three? Three kids? Oh. What?
是的  三個
Yeah, three.
是的  麗茲  一次生下的嗎
Yeah, Lizzy... At once?
是的  麗茲和她兩個小點的同胞兄妹阮和麗塔是一起來的
Yeah, Lizzy comes with two younger siblings, Juan and Lita.
等等  那我們  要領三個孩子嗎
Wait, wait. So we would have... three children?
不  兩個吧  也許  但是我們不可能能領養三個的
No. Two, maybe, but there's no way we can do three.
我的意思是  我曾想去看看  天啊
I mean, we wanted to meet... Oh, my gosh.
為什麼讓我們看這個  你是個混蛋
Why would you show us that? You're an asshole.
你為什麼要讓我們看這個  他們這麼可愛  這麼做不對
Why would you even show that? They're so cute. That's wrong.
認真聽  我們不會掩飾這件事  好嗎
Listen, we're not gonna sugarcoat it, okay?
麗塔是個  野蠻吵鬧的孩子
Lita is a... a wild, rowdy kid,
阮會有點脆弱  感情上有點敏感
and Juan can be fragile and a little emotional,
麗茲意志力很強  她不會輕易信任他人
and Lizzy is strong-willed and she won't trust easily.
這你能責怪她嗎  好吧  但是聽著
God, can you blame her? Well, but listen.
我們一般不會建議這次配對  要不是我們相信
We wouldn't recommend this match if we didn't believe
通過一些構造和感情
that with some structure and love
這三個孩子也許會綻放出花來  明白嗎
these... these kids could blossom, right?
是的  並且我們希望能夠讓他們擺脫現在的寄養
Yeah, and we're hoping to get them out of their current foster
情況
placement.
馬斯基一家也許會失去這飯票  凱倫  別說了
The Muskies might lose that meal ticket. Karen, please.
我們大多數的寄養父母是很棒的很有同情心的人
Most of our foster parents are really terrific, caring people.
但確實也有些人是為了酬勞而做這些
And, yes, there are people who do it just for the paycheck.
但馬斯基一家並不是虐待或者有害的
But the Muskies are not abusive or evil.
只是有一點  近親結婚
Just maybe a little... Inbred.
凱倫  沒有證據表明  你見過他們了
Karen, there is no evidence to... You've seen 'em.
我發誓他們看起來像兄妹  我分辨不出他們
I swear they look like brother and sister. I can't tell them apart.
不管怎麼說  我很樂意安排一個探訪
In any case, I'd love to set up a visitation,
除非你們還有別的顧慮
unless you have any other concerns.
只是一個探訪  那麼
It's just a visitation. So...
只不過  這真的沒問題嗎
I-I-It's just... Is it a problem...
你知道的  整個白色救世主這件事
You know, the whole white savior thing?
就像阿凡達那件事  阿凡達
Like the Avatar thing. Avatar?
你知道藍色的家伙是怎麼沒辦法擊退那些來采礦的人
You know how the blue guys couldn't fight off the unobtanium guys
直到白色的人出現了並偽裝成了一個藍色的人
until the white guy showed up and pretended to be a blue guy?
我想說的是  白膚色的夫婦接納著拉丁小孩
All I'm saying is, white-bread couple taking in little Latin kids.
人們會不會覺得我們不應該這麼做
Are people gonna think we shouldn't be doing that?
你知道嗎  我會重新把那些小孩放回去
You know what? We'll go ahead and toss these kids back into the system
然後給你們記下  僅領養白膚色小孩
and I'll just jot you down for "whites only."
不不不  我不是說  等下  不是  這不是
Come on. I didn't mean... Hey! No, that's not...
別寫下  僅領養白膚色小孩  這不是他的意思  這不是
Don't write "whites only." That's not what he meant. That's not
壓根不是我的意思
at all what I meant.
彼得  我感激你的文化敏感
Pete, I appreciate your cultural sensitivity,
但是我們這裡收納了各種膚色的小孩
but we have every color of kid in the system.
我們也有各種膚色的父母  每種膚色
And we have every color of parent. Every color.
只是不夠多  -父母數量不夠多
Just not nearly enough. Not nearly enough parents.
聽著
And listen.
你們會受到一些奇怪的眼光
You're gonna get some funny looks.
人們也會說些蠢話
And people are gonna say some stupid shit.
但是如果你們真的喜歡這些需要爸爸媽媽的孩子們
But if you're willing to love these kids who need a mom and dad,
而有人對此有異議
and somebody has a problem with that,
你只需要問問他們收養了多少的孩子
you just ask 'em how many goddamn kids they've adopted.
沒錯  說得對
Exactly. Hell.
我只是想說一下阿凡達  現在我們說完了  我沒問題
I just wanted to have the Avatar talk. Now we did, so I'm good.
好  棒極了
Oh, fantastic.
你準備好去見見孩子們了嗎  三個孩子嗎
You ready to meet three kids? Three kids?
是的  那好  我們會安排一下的
Yeah. All right. We'll set it up.
你好  過得怎麼樣
Hey. How's it going?
很好  過得很好
Uh, good. It's going really good.
我們是彼得和艾莉  我們知道  進來吧
Pete and Ellie. Yeah, we know. Come on in.
希望你能和那個孩子過得來  她認為她比所有人都好
Good luck with that one. She thinks she's better than everybody.
是啊  另外兩個就在後面閑逛
Yeah. The other two are jackassing around out back.
我們去商店
We'll be in the shop.
你好  瓦格納夫婦  你好嗎
Hey, uh, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner. How are you?
叫我們彼得和艾莉就好
Oh, uh, Ellie and Pete.
你不用叫我們瓦格納夫婦  不  沒事  很樂意
You don't have to call us the Wagners. No, please. Good to...
對不起  他們  沒事
Um, sorry about them. They're... Oh, please.
他們只是有點  像兄弟姐妹嗎
They just seem a little... Like brother and sister?
管好你的嘴  我們不是親戚關系
Pipe down with that crap. We are not friggin' related.
天殺的親屬關系
Friggin' related.
我真的會很想念他們的
I'm really gonna miss them.
前提是  如果你們  不不不  天啊
That is, if you... No. Please. Oh, my goodness.
我們第一次見面時你給我們留下了很好的印像
You made such a good impression on us when we met you,
我們想多了解你一點
we wanted to get to know you a bit more.
是的  見見你的兄弟姐妹
Yes! Meet your brother and sister.
他們就在外面  如果你們想跟著我  是的  對
They're right outside, if you guys wanna follow me. Yes! Yes.
阮  麗塔
Juan. Lita.
我想讓你們見見彼得和艾莉
I want you guys to meet Pete and Ellie.
你好  嘿  孩子們
Hi. Hey, guys.
我們現在就要住在你家了嗎
Are we gonna go stay at your house now?
我們見過你姐姐  她很棒
Well, we met your sister, and she's so awesome.
是的  她很酷  她正告訴我們關於你們的事
Yeah, she's really cool. She was telling us about you guys.
想和我一起去餐廳嗎
Want to play restaurant with me?
是的  我很樂意
Yeah, I would love to.
你的餐館在哪裡  就在那邊
Where's your restaurant? Right over there.
你的洋娃娃叫什麼名字  她的名字叫薯片
And what's your doll's name? Her name is Potato Chips.
我喜歡薯條  薯條是我最喜歡的
I love potato chips. Potato chips are my favorite.
很好的投球
Nice one.
我們能當快船隊嗎  我更喜歡湖人隊
Can we be the Clippers? I'm more of a Lakers fan.
哦  對不起  你不需要說對不起的  沒事的
Oh, uh, sorry. You don't have to say sorry. That's okay.
我們可以當快船隊  好的
We can be the Clippers. O-Okay.
我要投球了  你去欄板  好的  沒問題
I'm gonna shoot, you crash the boards. Yeah. Sure.
你是故意的  什麼
You did it on purpose! What?
你擊中我就因為我喜歡快船隊
You hit me 'cause I like the Clippers.
快船隊很棒啊  我們喜歡快船隊  你在開玩笑吧
The Clippers are awesome. We love the Clippers. Are you kidding me?
擺脫了布雷克 格裡芬真是太聰明了  那是一筆很好的交易
It was so smart to get rid of Blake Griffin. That was a great trade
對於球隊來說
for them.
我們愛極了快船隊  我都不會對他們感到膩煩
We're obsessed with the Clippers. I can't get enough of them.
他們太棒了  好吧
They're amazing. Okay.
我們可以玩玩捉迷藏嗎  你確定嗎  你流了很多血
Can we play hide and seek? You sure? You lost a lot of blood.
我喜歡捉迷藏  好吧  但只有我們  沒有女孩
I love hide and seek. Okay, but just us. No girls.
哦 好吧
Oh. Sure.
有點老套  但沒關系
It's not that progressive, but no problem.
麗塔 我們去玩過家家吧  好
Lita, should we go play restaurants? Yeah.
你來吧  我來藏你來數數好嗎
You're it. I'll hide and you count. Okay?
你確定你沒事嗎   我沒事
You sure you're okay? Yeah.
快點  開始數吧  數到20   好的
Go on, count. Count to 20. All right, buddy.
天爺啊
Oh, my God.
你最好別在餐館讓我下不來臺
You better not embarrass me at the restaurant.
薯條今天特別壞  壞女孩
Potato Chips has been bad today. Bad girl!
壞蛋  壞蛋  壞蛋
Bad, bad, bad!
別頂嘴  你個廢物
Don't talk back, you little beaner!
哦 額  我覺得
Oh! Uh... I don't think that's...
你知道嗎  她是從電視上學來的這些東西
You know what? She picks up that stuff off the TV.
是的  別這麼看我
Yeah. Oh, don't give me the look.
不能這樣說她的     不用你教我怎麼對我的孩子
Let's not call her bad names. Don't tell me how to treat my kid!
你是覺得自己做的比我好是嗎
You think you're better than me, huh?
彼得  如果你不想要孩子的話
Pete, if you don't want the kids,
我不會逼你的
I'm not gonna push you into it.
好吧
All right, look.
我實話告訴你吧
I'm gonna be honest with you, all right?
我也不知道  我只是認為當遇見我們的孩子的時候
I don't know, I just thought when we met our kids
就像冥冥之中有感應一樣 你明白嗎
that it would be like this cosmic connection, you know?
就是看一眼就知道是我們的孩子  就像我們兩個當初一見鐘情一樣
Like just take one look at them and just know, like when you and me met
是啊  完全同意
Yeah. Totally.
哇 哇 哇 你早就這麼認為的
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa. What, you didn't just know?
-嗯  哦  天哪
Hmm? Oh, my gosh.
怎麼了  你聽到我剛說什麼了  你不是才這樣想的
What? You heard what I said. You didn't just know?
不是啊 我很感興趣  但是 你知道的 我比較謹慎
No, I was interested, but, you know, I'm more cautious than you are.
真的  真的  你什麼時候這麼想的
Really? Wow. How long before you just knew?
幾個月前吧
A couple of months.
幾個月前  幾個月
A couple of months? How many months?
差不多 四
Like, four...
四個月  十四個月前
Four? ...teen.
十四個月前  天吶
Fourteen? Oh, my God!
我們沒結婚前我就知道了好嗎  這就是問題所在
I knew before we got married, okay? That's the point.
在收養他們這件事情上我們可沒機會適應一年
We don't have a year-long engagement on this thing.
如果我們同意的話  他們下周就會搬進來
If we say "yes," they're in our house next week.
你感覺到冥冥之中的聯系了嗎
Did you feel a cosmic connection?
沒有  我沒有感覺到
No, I didn't feel a cosmic connection.
我覺得我  我像是在給別人的孩子當保姆
I felt like I was... I felt like I was babysitting other people's kids
我同意
I agree.
同意什麼  同意你說的
With what? With you.
同意我想要孩子還是不想要孩子
With me wanting the kids or not wanting the kids?
你說的都同意   這算什麼回答
Whatever you want. That's not an answer.
那給我14個月讓我考慮一下  怎麼樣  來
Then just give me 14 months to think about it. How 'bout that? Come on
嗨
Hi!
這可不是家常便飯
It's not a potluck.
好了
All righty.
親愛的  幫我放一下這個 多謝
Honey, put those down for me. Thank you.
好了 來 各位
All right, come on, everybody.
親愛的  入座了 天吶
Honey, come on. Jeez.
好了  各位  手
All right, everybody, hands.
手 手 手  謝謝
Hands, hands, hands. Thank you.
閉上眼睛
Eyes closed.
我很感激有可愛的孫子孫女們
I'm thankful for my beautiful grandchildren,
包括那幾個非常幸運的孩子
including the... the very lucky kids
他們即將被兩個很棒的父母領養
that are soon to be adopted by two wonderful parents.
我也覺得很感激
I'm really thankful for that too.
這是非常值得鼓勵的  做的很好
That is really inspiring stuff, you guys. Well done.
其實  關於領養的事  我們
Yeah, about that. Actually, we...
我們決定暫時不領養了
Yeah, we've decided together not to move forward with the foster thing
是的  我們意識到我們還沒有好好的考慮清楚  所以
Yeah, we just realized we hadn't thought it through properly, so...
天吶  太棒了
Yeah! Jesus Christ. This is great news.
我是說  我們都是支持你們的  但是
I mean, we were all being supportive to your faces, but...
我們都覺得你們瘋了才會領養孩子
Yeah. We all thought you were out of your minds.
我什麼都沒說過 但是我真的很高興聽到你們說不領養了
I never said anything, but I'm thankful to hear this.
啥  為什麼
What? Why?
艾莉  別這樣  我們還牽著手呢   別 別 別
Ellie, let's not. We're holding hands. No, no, no, no.
我會很感激聽聽你們為什麼對這件事有意見
I would be thankful to know why you all have a problem with this.
嘿 我對此完全沒意見  我覺得很明智
Hey, I never had a problem with it. I think it's smart.
不用懷孕沒有荷爾蒙失調沒有情緒失控就有幾個孩子
Have a couple kids without the pregnancy and the hormones and the rage
閉嘴   艾莉
Stop talking. Ellie.
我是說我們會很感激
All I'm saying is that we're thankful
你和彼得會經歷為人父母
that you and Peter are gonna experience
疼愛你們親生的可愛的孩子 而不是
having the love of your own beautiful children rather than...
而不是什麼  簡  你說出來  我來說
Rather than what, Jan? Just spit it out. Hell, I'll say it.
而不是去收養什麼
Rather than just rolling the dice
罪犯或者癮君子的孩子
with the offspring of some criminal or drug addict.
實話說  我們很擔心我們孩子的安全
To be honest, we were worried about our real kids' safety...
啥  孩子們一塊出去玩  萬一你領養的孩子是
What? ...were they to hang out with your kids, if they're...
次品
Damaged goods?
我長這麼大  也有很多人認為我是次品
When I was growing up, a lot of people thought I was damaged goods too
彼得  我們不是在說你的
Pete, we're not talking about you, man.
我們說的是那些有過性騷擾的孩子
We're talking about crack babies and kids who have been sexually harassed.
性騷擾    你什麼意思  他們的父母使他們生來不堪嗎
"Sexually harassed"? What do you mean? Their parents made lewd comments?
你知道我在說什麼  自作聰明      睜開你的狗眼吧
You know what I mean, wiseass. Open your stupid eyes.
大家什麼時候都睜開眼了  吉米 還有所有在座的各位
How long have everyone's eyes been open? Kimmy, you of all people.
如果你們不能生孩子呢 請別把這種假設放在所有人身上
What if you can't have a baby? Do not put that out into the universe, please.
如果呢  你會怎麼辦
What if you can't? What are you gonna do?
你要是再因為孩子的事逼逼
If you don't quit being so nuts about this baby thing,
我發誓 我下午就懷孕
I swear to God, I'm gonna get pregnant again this afternoon
就為了惡心你
just to spite you.
你知道我能做到的  真的嗎
And you know I can do it. Really?
假的  哦
No. Oh.
如果我們的立場跟大家不同  那很抱歉
I'm sorry if we're not as politically correct as you guys,
但是孩子身上必須流著我們的血
but our baby has to be our blood.
是的 必須是 我的天 “我們的血”
Yes! Absolutely! Oh, my God. "Our blood."
這個血  在這的這個血嗎  那是什麼意思
This blood? This blood right here? What's that supposed to mean?
傑瑞  你說呢   有飯吃我已經很感激了  拉斯
Jerry, what do you think about this? I'd be thankful if we could eat, Russ.
你花了三十分鐘談論國家大事
You just spent 30 minutes talking about the deep state.
自己家的事你不管了嗎
You don't have an opinion on your own family?
不關我的事 多謝 老爸
None of my business. Thank you, Daddy.
我想告訴你們成千上萬的孩子
I would like you all to know that thousands of children
根本沒有家人一塊過感恩節
are spending Thanksgiving without any family at all.
但是現在我有點羨慕他們了  我知道你們愛我
And right now I kind of envy them. But I know you guys love me.
我知道我還有個地方吃火雞  我很感激
I know that I have a place to go to eat turkey and be thankful.
但是很多孩子沒有
But a lot of kids don't have that.
這根本不是他們的錯 還有他們不是次品
And it's not their fault! And they're not damaged goods!
所以我收回我剛剛說的話 我們還是會收養的
So forget what I said before. It is back on!
如果你沒意見的話 親愛的   咦哈 寶貝
If that's okay with you, honey. Yee-haw, baby.
咦哈  我們就是要收養這些孩子
Yee-haw. We're gonna adopt a whole shitwhack of kids.
誰他媽有意見可以滾蛋了  感激不盡
And I am thankful that whoever has a problem with it can fuck right off
阿門  阿門
Amen. Amen.
好了 又一個感恩節
Well, there goes another Thanksgiving.
你太酷了
You're crazy.
嗨 親愛的 我們回來了
Hi, honey. Here we are.
進來看看
Come in, look around.
這是肉球
This is Meatball.
聖誕樹
A Christmas tree?
這意味著聖誕老人會來嗎
Does that mean Santa comes here?
是啊 每年都來  耶
Yeah, every year. Yay!
所以  你們很有錢嗎  有錢 不
So, you guys are rich. What? Ri... No.
我們不是很有錢的  就還好
We're not rich. I mean, we're doing okay.
剛搬來的時候這裡還是個垃圾場
Well... When we got this house, it was a dump.
我們翻新了這個房子  艾莉全程設計
That's what we do. We renovate houses. Ellie did all the design work.
實際上  所有東西都是從舊貨集市和跳瘙市場買來的
Actually, everything is from swap meets and flea markets,
一點都不貴
and it's not that expensive at all.
那個是水晶 不好意思 天吶    對不起對不起
That's crystal! Sorry. Oh, my God. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
很抱歉  我不該把這個放在外面的
I'm so sorry. Uh, I shouldn't have left this out.
你們想去看看自己的房間嗎 走吧 我們去看看你們的房間
You guys want to see your rooms? Come on. Let's go check out your room
快看啊 小床還有小兔子  你覺得怎麼樣
Lookit! A bed and a bunny! What do you think?
我喜歡這個小兔子因為她穿著裙子
I love the bunny 'cause she has a skirt.
這些玩具是誰的  這些都是你們的
Whose toys are these? They're yours to share.
是的
Yeah.
樂高
Lego!
我能把我的熊放那邊嗎？
Can I put my bears in there?
當然了 當然可以
Sure. Of course.
哇  你有好多泰迪熊啊  這些是法庭熊
Wow, you have a lot of teddy bears. These are just court bears.
我們去一次家庭法庭就有一個熊
They get one every time we go to family court.
你能幫下我嗎  可以啊
Can you help me? Yeah.
哇 哇 哇  你看這個 麗塔
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Look at this, Lita.
麗茲  我帶你去你的房間吧
Lizzy, want me to show you your room?
好啊  就在這邊
Okay. Yeah. It's just here.
很抱歉還讓你們用這些塑料袋裝行李
I'm so sorry you have to carry all your stuff in these awful bags.
如果我們知道的話 不不不 沒關系的
If we knew... No, no, it's cool.
有趣的是 實際上可以以此判斷是不是一個領養的孩子
Fun fact: that's actually how you can spot a foster kid.
這種孩子一輩子都帶著個大袋子
The kid carrying her whole life in a Hefty bag.
這是個領養圈的玩笑
It's a foster joke.
在家你就隨意點
Well, make yourself at home.
是啊  這是你的地盤  你想怎麼樣都可以的
Yeah, this is your place. You can do whatever you want with it.
想在暀W貼海報嗎  塗個顏色嗎
Do you wanna put posters on the wall, you wanna paint it?
是啊  這個我們可以幫忙  20分鐘搞定
Yeah. Come on, This is what we do. We can knock that out in 20 minutes.
去下面的五金店  挑個你喜歡的顏色 你說呢
We can run down to the hardware store, pick any color you like. What do you say?
任何顏色都可以  你自己挑
Any color. Just pick a color.
你喜歡什麼顏色   什麼顏色都可以的
what color do you like?   Any color you want
你想怎樣都可以
Anthing you want
你挑顏色  我們刷上  你好像還挺喜歡綠色的
You pick a color, we're doing it. You'd look great in green.
天吶
Yeah.
覺得怎麼樣
What do you think?
哇  額  有點像最黑的那種巖石的顏色
Wow, uh, it's, yeah, darkest of the black tones.
是的 就是她選的顏色  -深壺黑  是嗎
Yeah, that's what she picked. Dark Kettle Black, huh?
我喜歡  酷斃了
I like it. It's really... dope.
我得去準備晚飯了  去吧
I'm gonna get dinner started. Okay.
她不喜歡這個顏色  我覺得她超愛這個色
She doesn't like it. I think she loves it.
好吧 你比我了解她
Well, you know her better than I do.
嘿  嗨 你們那邊弄好了嗎
Hey. Hey, you all done in there?
弄完了  她超喜歡
Oh, yeah. And... she loves it.
哦 太好了 她喜歡那個黑色的臥室那我就放心了
Oh, great. I'm so glad that she loves her black bedroom.
明天早上我帶阮和麗塔去哈丁登記
So, I'm gonna register Juan and Lita at Harding in the morning.
你帶麗茲去高中
And then you can take Lizzy to the high school.
你看見他們的鞋子了沒  我們明天得帶他們去趟商場
Did you see their shoes? We might want to take them to the mall tomorrow.
孩子們  吃飯了
Hey, kids, dinner!
什麼  從你嘴裡說出來簡直不可思議
What? That sounds insane coming out of your mouth.
我們有孩子了嗎  當然了 還是三個
Do we have kids? Yeah, three of 'em.
太酷了  簡直不能相信
That's insane! I don't believe it!
你不知道嗎  他們就在這裡啊
Did you not know that? 'Cause they're really here.
天吶  天吶  是真的
Holy shit. Holy shit. Yeah. Yeah.
他們就在這裡呢  我愛你
They're here. I love you.
怎麼了  再親一下  再親一下
What? Kiss again! Kiss again!
天吶
God. Mmm!
剛剛這個怎麼樣  再親一個  再親一個
What about that one? Kiss again! Kiss again!
那會很長很奇怪的
It's gonna be long and weird.
可以了吧  好了吧
How 'bout that? How 'bout that?
-快點  傻笑的小姑娘  請坐  -我去換個盤子
Come on, giggly. Sit down. I'm gonna shift the plates.
好了  好多好吃的  有漢堡 意面 還有
Great. We have everything. We have burgers and pasta and... Can
可以吃薯條嗎
we have potato chips?
準備洗澡吧
Let's get ready for the tub.
你們兩個  誰想
Uh, you two, come on. Who wants to...
嘿
Hey!
那個真的不是洗澡的玩具
That's not really a bath toy.
我不想要這個
I don't want this.
別 別  那個會 怎麼了 嘿 嘿
Oh, no! That's gonna... What? Hey! Hey!
我下次得弄個固定器
I'm gonna get a hamper next time.
嘿  下次
Hey, next time...
你需要  你看
You need...? Lookit!
抓 抓牢 別讓它沉下去
Grab... Hold it. Keep it over the sink, please.
沖水了嗎  寶貝
Did you flush, sweetie?
晚安  孩子們   晚安
Good night, kiddo. Good night.
好夢
Good night!
我們是不是應該給他們個晚安吻的   我也不知道
Should we give them a kiss good night? I don't know.
要不你去問問或者我們等  我去問下
Maybe you should ask, or should we wait? Should I ask?
我去問   你們可以直接進來哦
I'll ask. You guys are overthinking this.
不好意思  不好意思
Sorry, guys. Sorry.
晚安  晚安
Good night. Good night.
晚安
Good night!
那我們是不是也應該給麗茲個晚安吻
Should we kiss Lizzy good night?
我就不用了  晚安  哦 晚安 好孩子
I'm good. Good night. Oh. Night, kiddo.
好的 晚安
All right. Good night.
我們已經很努力適應他了
We try so hard to engage with him,
但是不管我們怎麼做  傑克就只是呆在他的房間裡
but no matter what we do, Jake just wants to hang out in his room,
打電話 說臟話 詛咒罵人
talking on his phone, swearing, taking the Lord's name in vain,
擺弄音樂 一待一整天
and cranking his explicit music till all hours.
又在學校打架
And he got into another fight at school.
還好沒有重傷幼兒園的其他小朋友
Thank heaven he didn't seriously hurt one of the other kindergartners.
五歲的小孩子有手機倒是沒什麼
I think maybe it's okay for a five-year-old to have a cell phone.
但是他有很多聯系人嗎
But does he have a lot of contacts?
我們試圖看下的 但是那是他親生媽媽給他的
We tried to take it, but his birth mother gave it to him,
我們一碰 就 嗯
and if we touch it, it's just... Mmm.
很抱歉  你們說的太對了
I'm so sorry. You are so right.
他根本不需要手機
He doesn't need a phone.
我們會再試試的 當然要試
We're gonna try again. Definitely try.
好了  彼得和艾莉十天前帶走了三個孩子
Okay, and Pete and Ellie took in three children ten days ago,
還有個十幾歲的
one of which is a teenager.
是的 一切順利
Yeah, it's going pretty good.
我們的孩子讓我們意識到我們之前的生活有多無聊
I think our kids made us realize just what kind of a rut we were in before.
不是說多無聊  就是一成不變 你們明白嗎
Not really a rut. Just the same old routine. You know?
上班  健身  吃飯  喝水  看電影
Work, go to the gym, grabbing dinner, drinks, the movies.
你們應該明白我在說什麼  不  我不明白
You know what I mean. No, we don't know.
她是在說我們之前的生活需要挑戰
I think she's just trying to say that we needed a new challenge,
需要打破這種單調的生活
maybe something to break up the monotony.
但是孩子們打破的不只是單調的生活
That's not the only thing they're gonna break.
我知道聽起來  我知道我們每個人都要經歷些痛苦
I know it sounds... I know everyone's going through tough stuff.
但是這些孩子  我覺得他們非常好 我們很幸運
But these kids, I think they're really good. We got lucky.
是他們比較幸運 是的，你中彩票了
They got lucky. Yeah, you hit the jackpot, lady.
大家別這樣
Guys.
有這麼好笑嗎
Why is this funny?
我猜他們可能是有點想到度蜜月的時候來例假了
I think they might be recognizing a little bit of a honeymoon period.
不不  是有點像  但是不像是來例假
No, we thought of that. But it doesn't feel like a period.
我是說也並不是完美的
Well, I mean, it's not perfect.
麗塔只吃薯條
Lita won't eat anything but potato chips.
我們正在想辦法解決  我是說我們也不是完美的父母
But we got a plan to work on that too. I'm not saying we're perfect
parents.
真的嗎
Are you sure?
我怎麼聽出來一點嫉妒啊
And I think I might be recognizing a little bit of jealousy.
各位  這可不是個好現像
It's not a good trait, guys.
我們在這干嘛呢
Okay, what do we have here?
啊  過聖誕節啊
Huh? Christmas!
這是啥  縫紉機  你覺得怎麼樣
What is it? It's a sewing machine! What do you think?
不好嗎 她不喜歡嗎 為什麼啊
No? She doesn't like it? Why not?
看著像個機器人啊 老弟  麗塔  你看這個大箱子
Looks like a robot, buddy! Lita, look at this big box!
哥們  它會說話還會走路  這可能是我的頭盔
Dude, it walks and talks. This could be my helmet!
那這些禮物呢   我要是有個機器人我會高興瘋的
What about the presents? I would've went crazy if I got a robot.
我玩那個機器人   這個可以當宇宙飛船
I'm playing with that robot. And this could be the spaceship.
我可以進去嗎  當然可以
Can I go inside? Sure.
嘿，孩子們，哇，你們真的很喜歡玩紙箱  哈
Hey, guys. Wow, you really like cardboard boxes, huh?
有人喜歡這個花了三小時弄好的玩具屋感興趣嗎
Is anybody interested in playing with the giant dollhouse it took
花了我三小時組裝
three hours to assemble?
是裝在大盒子裡的嗎
Did it come in a big box?
是的  在一個值200美元的大盒子裡
Yeah, it did. It came in a big $200 box.
我們走
Let's go! Let's go!
來吧  去拿箱子了
Come on. Let's go get the box.
聖誕節就是要玩箱子  沒錯
Christmas is boxes. Yes.
嘿  麗茲  這是給你的
Hey, Lizzy, this one's for you too.
聖誕快樂  哇哦
Merry Christmas. Oh.
另一個  是的
Another one. Yeah.
謝謝  聖誕  聖誕快樂
Thanks. Merry... Merry Christmas.
其實沒必要給我們這麼多
You didn't have to get all this stuff for us.
我懂  我懂  但我們很樂意
I know, I know, but we wanted to.
我們很興奮  是不是太過了
We were excited. Did we go overboard?
沒  沒  沒  呃抱歉
No, no, no! Um, I'm sorry.
我很開心
I'm happy. I am. I...
很開心看到麗塔和阮能收到
It's nice to see Lita and Juan get presents
不完全是陌生人捐的禮物
that weren't donated from total strangers, so...
嘿  麗茲  如果你想聊一些事
Hey, Lizzy, if you ever want to talk about anything...
我知道現在是聖誕節  你經歷過些事情
I know it's Christmastime and you may have memories and things.
不不不  我
Oh, no, no, no. I'm... I'm...
我很好
I'm good. I...
你知道嗎  我只是早上忘喝咖啡了
You know what? I just haven't had my morning coffee yet.
我現在去喝一杯
So I'm gonna get that.
你要嗎  好
Do you want some coffee? Sure.
感謝上天讓我們一起度過第一個聖誕
We want to thank the Lord for our first Christmas together.
感恩擁有這美味的晚飯  還有
And we want to give thanks for this lovely meal and also this, um,
這些超有意思的紙板盒子
bounty of super fun cardboard boxes.
阿門  阿門
Amen. Amen.
好了  大家開動吧
Okay. Tuck in, everybody.
我的薯片呢
Where's my potato chips?
今天晚上沒有薯片吃  抱歉小家伙
We're not having chips tonight, munchkin. Sorry.
我要吃薯片  麗塔
I want my chips. Lita!
彼得和我很努力地做了這頓飯
Pete and I worked really hard on this dinner.
有很多好吃的給你吃
There's lots of yummy food for you to eat.
不要  嘿  嘿  嘿
No! Hey, hey, hey.
麗茲  麗茲  等等  麗茲  別這樣  讓我來
Hey! Lizzy, Lizzy, please! Lizzy, no, okay? I've got this.
你為什麼對我吼  我想幫你啊
Why are you yelling at me? I'm just trying to help you.
我沒有吼你
I'm not yelling at...
呃我剛的確有吼  對不起  但是
I'm sor... I am. Just then I was. But it's... Look.
麗塔  不必聽麗茲剛說的  呃你說了什麼
Lita, don't do what Lizzy said. What did you say? C uatro? "Go to
回房間嗎
your bedroom"?
不  這詞意思是誇脫  就像一誇脫牛奶
No, cuatro means "quart." Like quart of milk.
她說  沒有薯片吃  但你可以喝
She said, "You're not gonna have a potato chip, but you will drink
牛奶
that milk."
總之  我們可以
In any case, we have this. It's fine.
好吧  行  好
Okay. Fine. Okay.
嘗一下肉吧  好麼
Let's try some of this meat loaf, okay?
不要  我要薯片  沒有薯片給你吃
No! I want my chips! You're not having chips!
寶貝我覺得她不會聽你的
I don't think she's getting on board with the plan, honey.
我不要這個  嘿
I don't want this! Hey!
你確定不給她點薯片嗎  不  不會給她的
You sure you don't wanna give her chips? No, we're not giving her chips.
麗塔  回來
Lita, stay right there!
我天  對不起  抱歉
Oh, God, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
沒關系  別哭  放松
No, it's okay. Don't cry. Relax.
當心腳下  抬腳
Watch your feet, okay? Raised feet!
我不是故意的  真的對不起
I didn't mean to. I'm so sorry.
把薯片給我
You give those to me.
嗷  冷靜  別哭
Ow! Ow. Calm down. Don't cry.
我要吃薯片
I want my chips!
別動  阮
Just stay there, Juan.
這土豆真的很好吃
These are really, really good potatoes.
我的天  你還好嗎  我天  等下
Oh, my God. Are you okay? Oh, God. Hold on.
麗塔  我去
Lita, duck!
你在做什麼  我在想辦法滅火阿
What are you doing? Look, I'm trying to put it out!
用番茄醬嗎  滅火
With ketchup? Put it out!
好了  麗塔呢
All right. Lita?
等下  什麼聲音
Wait, wh-what's that noise?
她為什麼這樣  上的課裡沒有教這個
Why is she growling? That wasn't in the classes. I got nothing for
怎麼辦
that.
她拿了刀
She's got a knife.
只是個海綿寶寶的刀  那也是刀啊
It's just a SpongeBob knife. It's still a knife.
把刀放下  寶貝
Just put the knife down, honey.
孩子  放下武器  好嗎
Look, kid, just put down the weapon, okay?
你們想讓我來處理  還是你們依舊可以
You guys want me to deal with this, or do you still got it?
讓她來幫忙吧  好嗎  好好好吧
Do you wanna let her jump in here now, please? Okay, okay. Fine.
行
Fine!
謝謝
Gracias.
艾莉  你得學一點西班牙語
Ellie, you gotta learn some Spanish.
小孩喝的牛奶為什麼用玻璃杯裝  對不起  我沒
Why would you give a kid milk in a glass cup? I'm sorry. I didn't.
她干嘛這樣  我討厭她
Why did she do that? I hate her!
才沒多久  他們已經討厭我們了
That didn't take long. They hate us already.
呃  確切地說  她是說討厭你
Well, technically, she said she hates you.
好好好  我要芭比
Okay, okay, okay! I want a Barbie!
這都不算是真的芭比娃娃
This isn't even a real Barbie.
之前聖誕老人都給了你一個真的芭比了
You've got a real Barbie that Santa gave you a few weeks ago.
聖誕老人給我的是胖的芭比  我要一個瘦的
Santa got me a fat Barbie! I want a skinny Barbie!
她不胖  那是健康的身材
She's not fat. She's body positive.
如果你把娃娃放下  我給你買超大的聖代吃
If you put the doll back, I'll get you a giant ice cream sundae.
所以你是在獎勵她這行為
So you're rewarding this behavior?
你在想什麼  你來處理吧
What are you thinking? You handle it.
阮  出來吧好嗎  別打我  別打我  我錯了
Juan, get out of there. Please? Don't hit me! Don't hit me! I'm sorry!
我沒有打他  好嗎  我從來沒打過他
I didn't hit him, okay? I never have hit him.
我不會打孩子的  我想要芭比
I would never hit a kid. I want a Barbie!
停下來  不然沒有午飯也沒有晚飯吃
Stop right now, or you're not getting lunch or dinner.
我們不是要讓誰挨餓  好嗎  我來處理
We're not starving people here, okay? I have this under control.
嘿麗茲  你個胖婊子
Yeah, Lizzy, you body-positive whore!
你完了 給我  把它給我
Okay, you're done. Gimme that. Give it to me. Just give me that now!
噢對  看起來一切盡在你掌握呢
Oh, yeah? Yeah, it really looks like you've got it.
掃進去  快點  不  我們不要這個
Scan it! Hurry! No! We're not doing this!
有人錄下來了嗎  彼得  你在哪裡  彼得人呢
Someone videotaping this? Pete, where are you? Where's Pete?
你完了  行你出去了  真是太感謝了
You're done. Oh, great. You're out there? Thank you so much.
寶貝  我把車開來了
Hey, sweetie. I brought the car.
節省你走路的時間  門前還有路要走
Saved you a little walking time. We had a front space.
好吧  但也很近了
Well, it's still closer.
嘿  彼得  看這個新娃娃漂亮吧  哇哦
Hey, Pete, look at my pretty new doll. Wow.
所以你還是妥協了  沒有
So you caved, huh? No, I did not cave.
我買給她的  只要四美金
I bought it for her. It was only four bucks.
我們能離開這裡了嗎  你個膽小鬼
Can we just get out of here, you coward?
臥槽  他們來了
Holy shit. There they are.
嘿  簡  傑瑞  他們到了
Hey, Jan, Jerry. They're here.
噢我天  車門蹭到了保時捷
Oh, man! Kid dinged a Porsche.
伙計你在做什麼  對不起  對不起
Dude, what are you doing? I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
好吧  別哭  好嗎
All right. Just don't cry, okay?
他需要留張紙條了
He's gonna have to leave a note.
就幫我把東西拿出來  麗塔  麗塔  寶貝
Just help get the stuff out of the back. Lita! Lita! Honey.
艾莉看起來像脫水了  看起來很糟糕
Ellie looks dehydrated. She looks bad.
我們帶了些披薩  阮  你在做什麼
We've got the pizza! Juan, whoa, whoa. What are you doing, bud?
噢對不起  噢天啊
Oh, sorry! Oh, Christ.
好暖和  嘿  把披薩放下
It's so warm. Hey, put the pizza down.
你不能那樣拿著  嗨  媽媽
You can't hold it like that. Hi, Mom.
嘿  爸爸
Hey, Dad.
你一定就是麗茲
You must be Lizzy.
恩  嗨  這是麗塔和阮
Yeah, hi. I'm Lizzy. Um, this is Lita and Juan.
你好  麗塔
Hello, Lita.
你好  阮
Hello, Juan.
我是外婆  胡恩  這是外公  胡瑞
I'm Grammy "Hw-an" and this is Grandpa "Hw-erry."
媽  可以正常點說話嗎
Mom, can you just talk like a normal person?
我喜歡J的發音
I like the way she says her J's.
拜托  很高級
Can you please? It's sophisticated.
給你  謝謝
Here you go, brother. Thanks, man.
我不敢相信  他們就和正常孩子一樣
I can't get over it. They look just like normal kids.
你覺得他們看起來應該像什麼  小海盜嗎
What did you think they were gonna look like? Little pirates?
不知道  他們太可愛了
I don't know. They're just so cute.
新學校怎麼樣
How is the new school?
挺好的  就像  呃  就像學校
It's good. It's like... It's, um... It's school.
哇  很棒
Yeah. Awesome.
那男朋友呢  有沒有心動
And what's the boy situation? Anything exciting?
別別  別煩她了
No, no. Hey, hey, leave her alone.
她不喜歡談這些
She doesn't like talking about that kind of stuff, so just go easy.
怎麼  你不喜歡的
What? You don't.
其實是有個叫雅各布的男生  是嗎
Actually, there's this one guy, Jacob. Yeah?
哇哦  很可愛的名字  雅各布  我挺喜歡的傑克
Wow, that's a cute name. Jacob. I like... Like Jake.
不不  是胡各布
No, honey, it's "Hway-cob."
對嗎  對嗎 胡各布
Right? Right? "Hway-cob."
不  不  就是雅各布
No, no, it's just Jacob.
對而且他不是可愛的感覺
Yeah, and he's not cute.
是帶點藝術氣息的成熟類型
He's more of like an artsy, old soul type.
我也從來都不喜歡可愛型的
I was never into the cute ones either.
恩  可愛不怎麼好
Nah. Cute's overrated.
是的  我也不喜歡  我從沒有交過性感的男朋友
Right? I didn't either. I've never had a hot boyfriend, ever.
閉嘴
Shut up!
?  你看起來就像只猴子  ?
? You look like a monkey ?
?  你聞起來也像是猴子  ?
? And you smell like one too ?
麗茲  飯桌上可以把手機放下嗎
Lizzy, can we put the phone away while we're at the table, like we
像我們之前說的那樣
talked about?
麗茲  請放下  把她手機給我
Lizzy, please. Give her the phone.
嘿朋友們快看  那邊有好戲看
Hey, guys, check it out. There's some shit going down. Lizzy, the
麗茲  手機
phone.
給我
Now.
那是她的親生母親嗎  好狠的一招
Is that her real mom? Yeah, that's a harsh move.
實際上  如果你看了福斯特的育兒準則
Actually, if you read your foster parent regs,
拿走任何私人物品是不被允許的
you know you're not allowed to take away any of my personal property,
所以
so...
這個表情  就是這個表情  我要去拿點番茄醬
It's the look. She's doing the look. I gotta get some ketchup.
彼得  你說過下次她再這麼過分你會采取行動的
Pete, you'd said you'd say something to her next time she acts all bitchy.
我從沒說過婊氣這次  是她說的  不是我
I never said the word "bitchy." It was her word, not mine.
因為你從來都不在  每一次我都是那個壞人
I am always the bad guy because you're never there.
我不會因為要工作而道歉
I'm not gonna apologize for working.
總要有人在你買的房子讓我們破產前
Somebody's gotta deal with that dump of a house you bought before it
搞定它
bankrupts us.
我買的嗎  你也喜歡啊  而且那根本不是關鍵
I bought? You loved it too. And that's not even the point.
關鍵是當你在現場  你任他們各種逍遙法外
The point is, when you are there, you let them get away with murder.
昨晚吃完飯麗茲不肯清理這點
I got on Lizzy just last night when she wouldn't clean up after
我就管教了她
dinner!
完美爸媽
Perfect parent, huh?
這很好笑嗎  基特  我認為我們都覺得挺有趣的
Is this funny, Kit? I think we're all enjoying this a little bit,
對不起  抱歉  沒關系
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's okay.
看白人吵架我從看不厭
I never get tired of watching white people fight.
我也是
Nor do I.
但是為什麼不冷靜一下
But why don't you calm down
除了互相責怪  告訴大家  關鍵的問題是什麼
and tell us, without blaming each other, what the main issues are.
好吧  麗塔一直
Well, Lita is just constantly...
我要   我不要
I want... I don't want to!
阮不肯動動他的腦子
And Juan just doesn't use his head.
解鎖下窗戶  而且如果我要說些什麼
Unlock the window! And if I say anything about any of it...
我真的很對不起  不是我的錯
I'm so sorry. It's not my fault.
麗茲最愛說的就只是  別管我了
Lizzy's favorite pastime is just... Just leave me alone!
謝謝讓我遲到
Thanks for making me late.
你是個混蛋
You're an asshole.
當我們試著教育兩個小的  不  那可是
God forbid we actually try to parent the little ones. No, no, that's
她的領地
her territory.
別忘了  麗茲十歲時  她的媽媽時不時就消失
Don't forget, when Lizzy was ten her mother would disappear for weeks
幾個禮拜
at a time,
留下麗茲獨自照顧阮和麗塔
leaving Lizzy to parent Juan and Lita all by herself.
她不會袖手旁觀讓你們倆全權負責
Yeah, she's not just gonna step aside and let you two take over.
你是說我們應該讓她來照顧兩個小的  你有
Are you saying that we should let her parent the kids? Are you
在聽嗎
paying attention?
她只有15歲  是個糟糕的家長  她需要成為孩子
She's 15. She's a terrible parent. She needs to be a kid.
現在你們要站出來努力成為父母
Now, you gotta step up and become the parents.
但你剛說她不會讓我們  是的她不會
But you just said she won't let us. Nope, she won't.
你知道麼  凱倫  大多數情況下你都很好
You know, Karen, you've been a godsend through most of this,
但我現在快被你惹惱了
but you're just about to piss me off!
情況不會改變直到你們達成共識
You won't get anywhere with her until you two get on the same page.
是嗎  沒錯
Right? That's right.
下次她再表現得不友善  試一下三R法則
If she's hostile with you again, maybe try using the three R's.
第一條  控制情緒
Okay? Number one: regulate.
麗茲  不如數到十  深呼吸
"Lizzy, why don't you take some deep breaths, count to ten."
第二條  拉近距離
Number two: relate.
我明白你很難受  沒有誰願意經歷這些
"I understand that you're upset. Nobody likes to feel this way."
很不錯  第三條  說明理由
That's good. Number three: reason.
麗茲  生氣是正常的
"Lizzy, it's okay to be angry.
但是威脅要在深夜我們睡著時
What's not okay is to threaten to slash our throats
給我們脖子來一刀就不怎麼好了
in the middle of the night when we're asleep."
抱歉  我是不是
I'm sorry, did I...?
這是實際上  我們的故事
That was actually us.Our story.
沒錯  上一次提到的
Yeah. Last session.
但小家伙沒有堅持要這麼做
The little guy didn't follow through with it though.
暫時沒有  -暫時還沒
Well, not yet! Not yet.
抱歉  我們不該笑
Sorry, but we shouldn't be laughing.
不  實際上擁有這樣的幽默感也是重要的
No, it's actually important to have a sense of humor about this kind of thing
沒錯  多笑笑  不然無法挺過去
Right. You gotta laugh or you'll never make it through this.
是的
That is right.
說到這  下一位輪到奧克托布
Speaking of which, next up we have October,
還沒有和孩子配對成功
who still hasn't been matched with a child.
終於還是有些好消息
Well, there's some good news.
我們一起決定負責哪部分家務
So, together we're all gonna decide which chore we'd like to do
每周再輪換
and then each week we'll mix it up.
我可以負責  喂米堡嗎  可以啊
Can I do "Feed Meatball"? Yes!
我想喂米堡  你可以下周喂他
I want to feed Meatball! You can feed him next week.
彼得  我希望她不是認真弄這些
Pete, I hope she's not serious about all this.
不只是她  是我們  並且我們是說真的
It's not just she, it's we. And we are. Very serious.
好吧  所以你是想我們來幫你們洗腳嗎  不  麗茲
Okay, so do you want us to wash your feet too? Oh, Lizzy.
都是狗屁  麗茲  嘿  等一下
This is bullshit! Lizzy! Hey, hey, wait, wait!
麗茲  讓我們  試些別的
Lizzy. Let's just... Let's... Let's try something else.
讓我們休息下  冷靜下來  深呼吸
Can we just take a moment, calm down, and take a few breaths?
好嗎
Please?
試試看
Try it.
很好  很好  我們明白你對這些感到很無語
Nice! Nice. And we hear you that you're frustrated with the chart.
對沒錯  我覺得很無語
Well, yeah. Yeah, I'm frustrated.
是的  無語很正常  我們也都有點沮喪
Yes! And that's okay to be frustrated! We're all frustrated.
讓我們想想下一次怎麼更好表達自己
So let's think about next time how we can express ourselves better.
好好  好吧
Okay. Okay. Well...
我不清楚  或許下次你們
I don't know, maybe next time you guys...
對我嘗試一下三R法則
try and use the three R's on me.
我可以吐一地  因為太惡心了
I could barf all over the ground because it's so nauseating!
我就知道這對她沒用
I knew it wasn't gonna work with her.
哇太棒了  你在家
Oh, good! You're home!
嗨
Hi!
媽媽  說了要發條短信或者打個電話啊
Mom, I told you to text or call.
你告訴我給你幾周安頓一下
You told me to give you a few weeks to settle in.
現在已經過了幾周了  而且我想看看我的孫子孫女
Well, it's been a few weeks, and I want to meet my new grandkids.
你肯定是麗茲吧  過來
You must be Lizzy. Come here!
不  她不喜歡  來這兒
No, she doesn't like it when you... Come here!
喔  我是你的奶奶珊迪
Oh! I'm your Grandma Sandy.
任何人想欺負你  他們都要先過我這關
Anyone ever starts shit with any of you, they have to deal with me.
我們現在是一家人了  我永遠是你堅強的後盾  你聽到了嗎
We're family now, and I got your back forever. You hear me?
媽媽  別緊張  拜托  哦  我的天吶
Mom, just take it easy. Please. Oh, my God!
我能看看他們嗎
Will you look at them!
阮  麗塔  這是珊迪  這是彼得的媽媽
Juan, Lita, this is Sandy. This is Pete's mom.
嗨  嗨
Hi! Hi!
真想把你們兩個吃了  我的大孫子怎麼樣啊
I could just eat you two up! And how's my baby boy?
噢
Ohh!
你好  親愛的  嗨
Hello, dear. Hi.
媽媽  給我們幾分鐘  我們正在開家庭會議呢
Mom, give us a few minutes. We were just in the middle of a family meeting.
太好了  我也是這個家庭的一員了
Perfect, because I'm a member of the family.
珊迪奶奶有一件事要宣布
Grandma Sandy has an announcement to make.
我給全家人都買了去六面旗主題公園的票
I got the whole family tickets to Six Flags!
耶  耶
Yay! Yay!
六面旗是什麼
What's Six Flags?
六面旗是什麼  媽媽  這個提議很好
"What's Six Flags?" Mom, that's such a nice offer.
但這裡的情況有點復雜  我們得把一切都處理好
But things have been a little chaotic around here, and we need things to be normal.
我來告訴你什麼沒有處理好  你的孩子不知道什麼是六面旗
I'll tell you what's not normal, is your kids not knowing what Six Flags is.
你的孩子們
Your kids.
媽  現在不是時候  我們沒有在說這件事  好嗎
Ma, it's just not a good time. So we're not doing this, okay?
我們沒有在說這件事  對嗎  我們在管理上達成共識了嗎
We're not doing this, right? We're on the same page because of the structure thing?
好吧  好吧
Yeah, yeah.
親愛的  是嗎  艾莉
Honey? Right, El?
我才沒屈服  哦  你屈服了
I did not cave. Oh, you caved.
麗茲看了你一眼  你就屈服了
Lizzy gave you the look and you caved.
也許我只想做個讓孩子開心的父母而不是個惡人
Maybe I just wanted to be the fun parent for once instead of being the bad guy.
我在試著做壞人  你不讓我做  好吧  是的  我很抱歉
I tried being the bad guy. You wouldn't let me. Okay, fine. I'm sorry.
但每個人看起來都很開心啊
But look how much fun everybody's having.
麗茲  她真的在笑  這太瘋狂了
And Lizzy, she's actually smiling. It's crazy.
嘿  你玩得開心嗎
Hey! Did you have fun?
你不必去玩兒童玩的那些項目
You don't have to go on the kiddie rides.
我喜歡刺激的  你想去
I love the big rides. You want to go on the...
嘿  麗茲  嘿  怎麼了
Hey, Lizzy! Hey, what's up?
很高興見到你  很高興見到你
Good to see you! Good to see you too!
嘿  嘿  怎麼了
Hey, hey. What's up?
呃  凱莉  莎凡娜  他們是我的  嗯
Uh, Kylie, Savanna, these are my, um...
養父母
fosters.
是的  是的  我們是她的養父母
Yeah, yeah. We're the fosters!
待會見  實際上  我們正要去水上樂園呢
I'll see you guys later. Actually, we were just gonna go on the water ride.
讓她和朋友一起去吧
Let her go with her friends.
她們可不想和你們兩個老家伙混呆在一起
They don't want to be stuck here with a bunch of old farts like you two.
她們想騎點刺激的東西  看看帥哥什麼的
They want to ride the big stuff and check out the hot boys.
這是一百元
Here's a hundred.
給自己買些紀念品和好吃的
Buy yourselves some souvenirs and junk food.
嗯嗯  謝謝  珊迪奶奶  謝謝
Uh-huh. Thanks, Grandma Sandy. Thanks!
好吧  酷
All right, cool.
呃  什麼時候回你家
Uh, meet you guys at... What time are we going back to your house?
我們回自己的家  我們都住在那裡  七點
We're going back to our house, where we all live, at 7:00!
好的  到時候見  再見
Okay, I'll see you then. Bye!
媽媽  你在干什麼  你不能  哦  不
Mom, what are you doing? You can't... Oh, no!
小阮被垃圾桶卡住了
Little Juanny's upchucking in the trash bin!
你沒事吧  寶貝兒
You all right, peanut?
把剛才吃的漏鬥蛋糕都吐了嗎
Was it all the funnel cakes we ate?
哦  哦  哦
Oh. Oh, oh.
我知道她收到了這些短信  我能看到這些點
I know she's getting these texts. I can see the dots.
也許她跑掉了  也許她出了什麼事
Maybe she ran off. Maybe something happened to her.
不  她沒有  她只是把我們又當作一對養父母了
No, she didn't. She's just treating us like another set of fosters.
好啦  再見
All right, bye.
謝謝你送我回來  我愛你
Thanks for the ride. I love you!
我要當個壞人了  注意點  再見
I'm the bad guy. Watch this. Bye.
再見  嘿
Bye! Hey!
你到底去在哪兒了  我們去看電影了
Where the hell were you? We went to the movies.
時間長了點  沒什麼大不了的
And it ran a little bit later. It's not a big deal.
你就不能花五秒鐘來讓我們知道你沒有被人謀殺嗎
You couldn't have taken five seconds to let us know nobody murdered you?
好吧  你猜怎麼著   你被禁足了
Well, guess what? You're grounded.
我被禁足了  是的  你被禁足了  因為我剛把你禁足了
I'm grounded? Yeah. You're grounded. Because I just grounded you.
在你沒有被禁足之前  你沒事
Before you weren't grounded, you weren't anything,
然後我說了我剛才說的話  現在你被禁足了
and then I just said that thing that I said, and now you're grounded!
我們已經等了你一個小時了  我來當壞人  冷靜
We've been waiting one hour for you! I'm the bad guy. Calm down.
他來當壞人  你哪兒也不能去了
He's the bad guy. You're not going anywhere.
你完了  完了
You're done! Done!
不想聽  你知道嗎
Don't want to hear it! You know what?
我九歲的時候住在一個破房子裡
When I was nine I lived in a crack house.
所以我非常肯定電影院是個安全的環境
So I'm pretty sure the multiplex is a comparatively safe environment.
哦  不  不  就因為你有過麻煩不代表這次就沒事了
Oh, no. No. You don't play that trouble pass card with us.
你完蛋了  小姑娘
Your butt's in a sling, missy!
哦  珊迪奶奶  我忘了  什麼
Oh, Grandma Sandy, I forgot. What?
我給你帶了  嗯
I got you, um...
哦  天吶
Oh, sweet Jesus.
看看這個  我每天都要穿著它
Will you look at this? I'm gonna wear it every day.
哦  過來
Oh, come here.
你知道  這提醒了我
You know, this reminds me
彼得和他那些狐朋狗友偷過一輛披薩卡車
of when Pete and his degenerate friends stole a pizza truck.
她很好  她很好  哦  天哪
She's good. She's good. Oh, God.
你們倆要整晚都站在那兒嗎
Are you two gonna stand there all night,
還是我們要讓孩子們按時睡覺呢
or are we gonna try to get these kids to bed at a decent hour?
你還記得我告訴過你我們做的還遠遠不夠嗎
You remember I told you we weren't special enough for this?
我們做得很好  你說我們是墨守成規的
We were doing fine. You said that we were in a rut.
也許我們被寵壞了  不喜歡一成不變的生活
Maybe we were spoiled and didn't appreciate the rut.
那種生活簡單而安靜  你知道  我有點懷念了  但你非要當個媽媽
The rut was easy and quiet. You know, I miss the rut. But you had to be a mommy.
去和青少年談談是誰的主意
Whose idea was it to go and talk to the teenagers?
我們不能找個不會發表意見還不會穿丁字褲的小孩吧
We could've had a toddler who doesn't have opinions and thong underwear.
什麼  你把我們推進了下一個層次的爛攤子裡
What? You pushed us into some next-level shit!
聽著  我們不能在這裡互相挑釁
Look, we can't start turning on each other here.
如果我們保持冷靜一起戰鬥
If we just stay calm and we work together,
我們可以找到辦法把這些小混蛋趕出我們的房子
we can find a way to get these little assholes out of our house!
現在我們正在說啊
Now we're talking!
我就是這麼想的  你好
That's exactly what I was thinking. Hello!
我非常討厭他們  我也是  他們最壞了
I hate them so much. Me too. They're the worst.
他們太忘恩負義了  我們為他們做了一切
They're so ungrateful. We're doing everything for them.
他們卻他媽什麼都不能給我們  是吧
And they could give two shits. Right?
但你猜怎麼著  他們還沒有被正式收養
But guess what? They're not adopted yet.
不  不  他們沒有
No. No, they're not.
我們可以
We could just...
把他們就送回去
put 'em back.
我是說  是的  我們看起來像世界上最差的人  但是
I mean, yes, we would look like the worst people in the world, but...
是的  我們會的  現在每個人都認為我們是聖人
Yeah, we would. And right now everybody thinks we're saints.
我知道  我喜歡這一點  我真的很喜歡這一點  這是唯一的優點了
I know. I love that part. I do love that part. That's the only good part.
我有個主意
Just an idea.
如果我們說有親戚來了呢
What if we say that some relatives came forward?
法庭把他們帶走了  我們無能為力
The courts took 'em. There's nothing we could do.
對吧  我們再擠幾滴眼淚  表現得非常難過
Right? We squirt a few tears, we act super devastated.
那很好  那很好  那非常好
That's good. That's good. That's very good.
然後我們就有了干凈的房子和約會之夜
And we get our clean house and date night back.
每個人都為我們感到難過
And everybody feels sorry for us.
是啊  對吧
Yes! Right?
也許會收些禮物
Get some presents maybe.
我們永遠不會這麼做的
We're never gonna do that.
不
No.
這是個好主意  但我們
It's a nice thought, but we're...
我們被困住了  不是嗎  是的  我們被困住了
We're stuck, aren't we? Yeah, we are.
你知道  我們必須承認我們犯了一個嚴重的錯誤
You know, we gotta just accept that we made a terrible mistake
我們的生活現在大部分都會很糟糕
and our life is mostly gonna suck now.
晚安  親愛的
Good night, honey.
好了  板條兩邊各有一個釘子
All right, one nail on each side of the slat.
好的  在兩端都有  可以嗎
Okay. On both ends. Okay?
看  是的  很好
"Look." Yes, excellent.
好的  繼續  把這些拼出來
Okay, keep going. Get the words for me.
你在做什麼  你想進來嗎  你想和麗茲打個招呼嗎
What are you doing? You want to get in? You wanna say hi to Lizzy?
說曹操曹操到
Speak of the devil.
他們在這裡干什麼
What are they doing here?
你從沒說過我不能讓任何人來玩
You never said I couldn't have any people over.
每個人都知道被禁足的時候是不能有人過來的
Everybody knows you can't have people over when you're grounded.
你也知道  因為他們顯然是從窗戶進來的
You know that too, because they obviously came in through the window.
順便說一下  這個地方太惡心了
This place is disgusting, by the way.
天吶  真是個納粹婊子  你剛才說我什麼
God, what a Nazi bitch. What did you call me?
我不知道  你就像個納粹婊子
I don't know. You just seem like a Nazi bitch.
出去  現在
Get out. Now.
出去  你們兩個  出去  去吧  現在  不  你滾出我的房間
Out. Both of you, out. Go! Now! No, you get out of my room.
不  不  我要你在這黑屋子裡待著  這些人要走了
No, no, I'm staying in your black room. These guys are leaving.
不  從窗戶出去  造反者們  哪裡來的哪裡去
No, out the window, Pussy Riot! Way you came in!
出去  現在  臥槽
Out, now! Holy shit!
出去  出去
Out! Out!
哦  你真是瘋了
Oh! You're literally crazy!
是你把我逼瘋的  哦  我的天  你在做什麼
You're driving me crazy! Oh, my God. What are you doing?
你看起來像個精神病患者  發動汽車
You're acting like you're a psychopath. Start the car.
裡面發生了什麼  麗茲  拜托  我說你被禁足了
What is going on in there? Lizzy, please, I said you're grounded.
你要去哪裡  我要打電話給我的社工
Where are you going? I'm calling my caseworker.
好主意  嗯
That's a good idea, huh?
讓警察來  讓你的弟弟和妹妹打包他們的小熊
Get CPS to come, make your little brother and sister pack up their court bears
和垃圾袋然後搬回莫斯科
and trash bags in the middle of the night and move them back to the Muskies?
那對他們真好  那也比你好
That'll be really good for them. Better than you.
不  不比我好  我受不了你了  你能處理一下嗎  彼得
No! Not better than me! I can't with you. Can you please deal with her, Pete?
嘿  麗茲  你要  我們真是好人
Hey, Lizzy, you're gonna... We're really good people!
我們只想給你一個完美的家  這樣不對嗎
We just want to make a nice home for you. Is that so wrong?
你只是一個想做慈善收養孤兒的白人女士
You're just another white lady who wants to adopt little charity orphans
這能讓你對自己感覺良好
to make you feel good about yourself.
彼得  你告訴她我是什麼人  告訴她
Pete, you tell her what my nationality is! Tell her!
嗯  事實上  她是
Well, actually by blood she is...
我有八分之一的科曼奇族血統  好嗎  所以我不是白人
I'm one-eighth Comanche, okay? So I'm not that white!
我現在看起來有自我感覺很好嗎
And do I look like I feel good about myself right now?
好吧  那告訴我  請告訴我
Okay, then tell me! Please tell me!
你為什麼突然有了想要收養孩子的沖動
Why did you suddenly feel the urge to get foster kids?
因為我們  是  我是說  我
Because we... It was... I mean, I...
彼得  求你了  就是這樣  不  我
"Pete, please?" Exactly. No, I...
嘿  你哪兒都不能去  站住
Hey, you're not going anywhere. Stop right there!
我是認真的  別打開那扇門
I mean it. Don't open that door.
嘿  別上那輛車  你聽見了嗎
Hey! Do not get in that car. You hear me?
別關那扇門  我是認真的
Don't shut that door. I mean it!
很好  現在我們能進去談談這個嗎
Good. Now can we just go inside so we can talk about this?
阮  馬上放下
Juan, drop it right now!
你在做什麼  把它拿出來
What are you doing? Take it out!
-不  最好在到醫院之前別動它  你沒事的  伙計  我們在呢
No, better to leave it in till we get to the hospital. You're okay, buddy. We're here.
我們在這裡  你會沒事的
We're here. You're okay.
堅持一下  我得把它包起來
Stay still. I got to wrap it up.
放輕松  我們馬上送你去醫院  好嗎  你是
Relax. We'll get you there in one second, okay? You're...
哦  親愛的  阮會沒事的  來吧
Oh, honey, Juan is gonna be okay. Come on.
你知道嗎  告訴女孩們我們需要他們的車  現在
You know what? Tell the girls we need their car. Now!
出來  快點  動起來  快點
Get out! Move your ass! Come on!
我在呢  孩子  我在呢  -上車  上車  上車
I got you, buddy. I got you. Get in, get in, get in.
大家系好安全帶  系好安全帶
Seat belts on, everybody! Seat belts on.
你是個勇敢的孩子  聽到了嗎  看著我  你真勇敢  對吧
You're a brave boy, you hear me? Look at me. You're so brave. Yeah?
你做的太棒了  伙計  我們就在這裡呢
You're doing such a good job, buddy. We're right here.
你好  嘿  救救他
Hello! Hey, help, please.
發生什麼事了  他腳上有根釘子
What happened? He's got a nail in his foot.
我不想拿出來以防萬一
I didn't want to take it out, just in case.
那很聰明  把他放在這個輪床上
That was very smart. Put him right on this gurney.
嘿  伙計  沒事的  伙計  我們在這呢
Hey, buddy. It's all right, buddy. We're here.
你是母親嗎  是的  哦  我是他的養母
Are you the mother? Yes. Oh, I'm his foster mom.
好的  這邊走  爸爸
Okay. Right this way, Dad.
嘿  伙計  你叫什麼名字
Hey, buddy, what's your name?
阮  我們要把這個清理干凈  給你打一針麻醉劑
Juan, we're gonna clean this off, give you a little anesthetic,
然後把釘子拿出來
and then take this nail out.
握住我的手  可能會有點疼  看著我
Hold my hand. Gonna be a little pinch. Look at me.
抓住我的手  抓住我的手  有點刺痛
Hold my hand, hold my hand. A little bit of a sting.
停下  住手  快好了
Stop! Stop! It's almost over.
就是這樣  好了  好了  好了
That's it. It's done! It's done. It's done.
我想我們應該帶麗塔去大廳
I think we should take Lita to the lobby.
你想和她一起去還是留下來陪阮呢
You want to go with her or stay here with Juan?
你抱著她吧
You take her.
過來  嘿  我就在這兒
Come here. Hey, I'm right here.
沒事了  你真勇敢
He's okay. You're so brave.
你做得太好了  伙計
You're doing so good, buddy.
所以他不必穿石膏什麼的  只是縫線嗎
So he doesn't have to wear a cast or anything? It's just stitches?
是的  好吧  這是個好消息
Yeah. Well, that's good news.
這是怎麼發生的呢
And how did this happen?
這是我的錯  我走開了  把釘槍留在了那裡
It was my fault. I walked away, and I left the gun there.
阮剛把它撿了起來  不  不是他們的錯  是我的錯
Juan just picked it up. No. It wasn't their fault. It was mine.
我想開車離開  但我不該離開
I was trying to leave in a car and I wasn't supposed to,
然後他們分心了  然後我對阮大喊大叫
and then they got distracted, and then I yelled at Juan,
然後他手上的釘槍掉到了腳上
and he dropped the thing on his foot...
別扯淡了  我不應該把釘槍留在那兒
Don't be ridiculous. I should never have left the nail gun there.
彼得  閉嘴  這就是他們讓孩子搬走的原因  好嗎
Pete, shut up! This is the kind of stuff they move kids for, okay?
這不是他們的錯  他們什麼都沒做
It wasn't their fault. They didn't do anything.
我應該是犯了錯的人  沒關系
I should be the one getting in trouble right now. It's okay.
你為什麼不過來這裡呢  抱歉
Why don't you come on over here? Excuse me.
我們來談談發生了什麼
And, uh, let's talk about what happened.
所以  呃  沒有人會被搬走
So, uh, nobody's being moved.
嘿  怎麼了
Hey. What's wrong?
呃  我不知道  今天早上我剛醒來
Uh, I have no idea. I just woke up this morning and...
該死的
Damn it.
你知道嗎  我想我能幫忙
You know what? I think I can help.
我有一個
I have a...
我有一個很棒的梳子  要不要我
I have this really great detangler. You want me to...?
當然  是的  是的  管他呢  當然了  是嗎
Sure, yeah. Yeah, whatever, yeah. Yeah?
好吧  這裡
Okay, here.
坐下來  我會  是啊
Have a seat, and I'll... Yeah.
好的
Okay.
哇  怎麼會這樣  我不知道
Wow. How'd this happen? I don't know.
是啊  如果拽到頭發了就跟我說聲  好嗎
Yeah. Just let me know if it pulls, okay?
好的  搞定了
Okay. That's good.
好多了  是吧  哦  哇  是啊  謝謝了
Better, yeah? Oh, wow. Yeah. Thank you.
讓我再把它弄順點
Let me just smooth it out for you.
謝謝了
Thank you.
沒關系  一切都過去了
No problem. It's all gone.
都準備好了嗎  準備好了
You all set? Yep.
嘿  謝謝你的午餐  沒關系
Hey, thanks for the lunch. No problem.
哦  那是雅各布嗎
Oh, is that that boy Jacob?
剛剛撿了垃圾的那個
The one that just picked up that bit of trash?
別大驚小怪  沒有  我為什麼要大驚小怪呢
Don't freak out about it. No! Why would I freak out about it?
就像你說的  他看起來像一個藝術型的人
He looks like an artistic type, like you said.
你真的這麼認為嗎  當然了
You think so? Definitely!
看看那張臉  是啊
Look at that face. Yeah.
挺有責任心的  知道把垃圾撿起來
Conscientious. Picking up trash.
是啊  是  他是
Yeah. Yeah, he is. Yeah.
好的  祝你有愉快的一天  謝謝  你也是
Well, have a good day. Thanks. You too.
好的  好的
Okay. All right.
小心你的腳  阮  再見  麗塔
Careful with your foot, Juan. Bye, Lita.
你看到了嗎
Well, did you see that?
肯定開始不那麼恨我了  對吧
Definitely starting to hate me a bit less, right?
也許吧
Maybe.
嗨  麗茲  嘿  查利
Hi, Lizzy. Hey, Charlie.
嗨  雅各布
Hi, Jacob.
怎麼了 小寶貝  沒什麼
Wassup, baby girl? Nothing.
你怎麼樣  我挺好  收拾你的爛攤子
How you doing? I'm good. Cleaning up your mess.
你為什麼不在給我惹麻煩之前早點進學校呢
Why don't you get into school before you get me in trouble.
好的  沒問題
All right, fine.
聯系我  -沒問題
Text me. Okay.
嗨  親愛的  嗨
Hey, hon. Hey.
她做得怎麼樣  她挺好的
Hi. How's she doing? She's good.
噢對了  還有個事兒
Oh. Yeah. And check this out.
我今天到早了  麗茲看到我  然後就
I got here early, Lizzy saw me, and she came over and just starts
開始說話了
talking.
跟你說話嗎  對啊
To you? Yeah!
不是那種乖女孩的聊天  也不是平常的冷戰
Not, like, full-on girl talk, but not the usual silent treatment either.
她居然還跟我講了那個叫雅各布的男孩
She was telling me about that kid Jacob,
還有他不怎麼說話  她不知道他是不是喜歡她
and how he doesn't say much so she can't tell if he likes her.
下一刻我就進入了媽媽模式  給她建議  比如
Next thing I know I'm in full mom mode, giving her advice, like,
對害羞的男孩有時候你要邁出第一步
"Well, sometimes with the quiet types you'll have to make the first move."
你說什麼第一步  你讓她對男孩邁出第一步
You said "make a move"? You told her to make a move on a boy?
這是個好男孩  寶貝  相信我
This kid is harmless, baby. Trust me.
沒想到她居然會喜歡他  我想她愛上一個壞男孩
I'm thrilled she even likes him. I totally pegged her for the bad boys.
怎麼回事啦  阮弄壞了薯條
What happened? Juan broke Potato Chips.
別哭別哭  我可以修好她的  看  修好啦
Calm down. I'm gonna fix her, okay? Here you go. See?
謝謝  耙耙
Thanks, Daddy.
你有聽到嗎  她剛剛叫我爸爸
Did you hear that? I just got my first "Daddy"!
你作弊了吧
That's... You suck!
不公平  我也要  嗨  親愛的
No fair! I want some of that. Hey, honey.
麗塔  我有什麼可以幫到你嗎  沒有
Lita, can I help you with anything? Nope!
什麼沒有  你是跟我說話嗎  我是誰啊
No, what? Are you talking to me? Who am I?
艾莉  阮  寶貝  來這兒
Ellie. Juan. Buddy, come here!
來這兒  乖兒子
Come here, Son.
你的東西好吃嗎  我叫你兒子你可以接受吧
How's your foot? You okay? You okay if I call you "Son"?
當然啦
Sure.
麗茲去哪兒了  就在那兒  看得到嗎
Where's Lizzy? Right there. See her?
噢當然  她就在那兒
Oh, yeah, she's right there.
她剛來這兒  然後翻了個底朝天
She just comes out here, she takes all this stuff out,
她甚至不會用一秒鐘
and she can't bother with the one second it takes
關上這個門或者放臟東西到水槽裡
to close a stupid door or put anything in the sink.
發生了什麼  我早上在馬桶裡找到我的梳子
What happened? I found my hairbrush in the toilet this morning.
什麼鬼  我都說了不是我放的
What? I told you that wasn't me!
不是你是誰  是我留在浴室給你用的
Of course it was you. I left it in the bathroom for you.
阮和麗塔都還沒起床  我起床啦  吵鬧小姐
Juan and Lita aren't even up yet. I'm up now, Miss Noisy Pants.
對不起啊我的小寶貝  我以為我們關系在變好
I'm sorry, sweetie. I thought we were really connecting.
我留在那給她用還貼了個愛心小便貼
I left it there for her with a nice little note, with hearts on it and stuff.
我滴天哪  不是我扔進馬桶的
Oh, my God. I didn't do it.
哇哦  你好  這是什麼鬼
Wow. Hello. What is that?
你穿著這衣服是去脫衣舞俱樂部嗎
You're wearing that? Are you going to a strip club?
對不起  我不會像你穿得像個焦慮的沙雕那樣
Sorry I don't dress like an uptight douche like you.
你不能這樣和我老婆說話  這是安泰勒閣樓的衣服誒
You don't talk to my wife like that! This is from Ann Taylor. Loft!
安泰勒閣樓  美國第一行政品牌
趕緊去穿外套  越多越好
You know what? Go put some clothes on, a lot of them.
然後上車  今天早上我送你  我滴天哪
Then get in my truck. I'm driving you this morning. Oh, my God!
你們真的很吵誒
You guys are so annoying!
去換衣服  這又不是什麼大事兒
Change the clothes. It's not that big of a deal.
嗨  我穿得像個沙雕嗎
Hey. Do I dress like a douche?
沒有  看著她讓她上我的車  再見啦  耙耙
No. Make sure she gets out to my truck. Bye, Daddy.
再見  小寶貝
Bye, sweetie.
嚇死我了
Oh, my goodness. Oh.
怎麼回事兒啊
Hey, what's that? Oh!
你沒事吧
You okay?
真的太羞恥了
That's a shame.
我們在干嘛呢  走啦
What are we doing here? Let's go.
我會遲到的  你知道嗎
I'm gonna be late for school, you know.
進來吧
Come on.
哦謔  所以你現在是體罰我咯
Okay. So you're punishing me with manual labor.
我任何時候都比你更努力地活著
I've worked harder than you've ever...
嗯我知道  你很了不起
Yeah, I know, you're a badass.
這不是懲罰  好吧  嗨
This isn't a punishment, okay? Hey!
我是Stewart  你應該就是  你好嗎
I'm Stewart. You probably... You... What's up?
斯圖爾特別再跟她說話好嗎
Stewart. Don't ever talk to her again, okay?
計劃有變  你去吃午餐  這才八點十五分誒
As a matter of fact, go to lunch. It's 8:15.
好吧  午餐時間
Okay. Lunch it is.
過來
Come on.
把這些穿上  什麼鬼
Put these on. What?
別廢話  穿上
Just put them on.
麗茲我知道你很生氣
Lizzy, I know you're angry.
不爽我們  不爽這個世界  可能也有點不爽你自己
At us, at the world. Maybe at yourself a little bit.
我不知道  你又不肯說話
I don't know, and you're not talking.
事實是  我生氣的時候也不想說話
Truth is, when I'm pissed, I don't like to talk about it either.
但你知道我生氣會做什麼
But you know what I do like to do?
啊  我生氣時喜歡搞破壞
Oh! I like to break shit.
真的嗎
R... Really?
這屋子裡的任何東西
Anything in this room.
砸起來  嗯嗯
Swing away. Okay.
怎麼樣  感覺爽嗎  爽啊
Huh? How'd that feel? It felt good!
沒騙你吧  嗯嗯
Feels good, huh? I told you. Yeah.
停停停  別浪費  現在我想你幫我個忙
Now... Whoa, whoa! Don't waste it, all right? I want you to do me a favor.
我需要你想些真的能搞毛你的事
I need you to think about something that really pisses you off.
明白沒  明白了
You got it? I got it.
好的呢  砸它
Let's see it. Bust that shit up.
爽
Yes!
爽吧 你喜歡不  當然  非常爽
There you go. You like that? Yeah, that was good.
好  接著來
All right, come on.
爽吧
There we go. Yes!
哈哈雙殺
Ho-ho! Double shot!
爽完了吧
You like that?
超爽的
That was cool.
所以今天不上學了嗎
So no school today, huh?
皮特帶我去你們正在裝修的屋子了  嗯哼
Pete took me to the house you're flipping. Hmm.
我們做了些了不得的工作  嗯  挺好的
We did some demo work. That's cool.
嗨嗨嗨  過來
Um, hey, hey, come on.
那個馬桶裡的梳子嗎
About that hairbrush?
我親媽以前是幫我梳頭的
my mom used to brush my hair...
我不知道  很對不起
and I don't know, I'm sorry.
沒關系的  我也有錯
It's okay. I'm sorry too.
不不  你沒有錯  才不是呢  真的對不起
No, you have no reason to be sorry. No, I'm really sorry.
好
All right.
我現在去收拾干凈  如果你需要的話梳子在馬桶裡
I'm gonna go clean up. Hairbrush is in the toilet, if you need it.
干得漂亮
Good one.
謝謝
Thank you.
你要這樣轉動胳膊才行
You wanna rotate like this, okay?
對  就是這樣
Yeah.
阮打我了
Juan hit me!
啊 我的天哪
Oh, no. Oh, God!
嘿  三號球員  把你媽叫過來
Hey, number three, where's your mother?
我沒事  沒事就好
I'm okay. Okay.
我沒有打她
I didn't hit her!
阮你把我手機藏哪兒了
Juan, where did you put my phone?
我沒有拿你的手機  我真的沒有
I didn't take your phone! No, I didn't!
好  第一次嘗試
All right! First try!
-Tres  -Tres
Tres. Tres.
學會了沒  爸 爸 爸
There you go. Dad, Dad, Dad!
拿好了阮
There you go, Juan.
吐出來  吐出來
Spit it out, spit it out!
接住  水  不  我們需要冰
Here, water! No, we need ice!
水來了 水來了  天哪
Water, water. Here. Oh, gosh.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  小寶貝
Hey, buddy.
嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿  一切安好呢小寶貝  你發噩夢了嗎
Hey. It's okay, sweetie. Did you have a bad dream?
嗯嗯  真的啊
Yeah. Yeah?
沒有事的  你在被窩裡很安全
You're okay. You're safe and sound in your bed.
你四肢健在呢
You're good.
晚安啦  小寶貝
Good night, buddy.
晚安  嘛嘛
Good night, Mommy.
什麼
What?
你剛剛說什麼了
What did you say?
阮  能在說一次嗎
Juan, what did you say?
你是不是叫我媽媽了  阮
Did you say something, Juan?
嘿  阮  你是叫我媽媽了吧
Hey, Juan, what did you say?
阮
Juan!
阮  再叫我一次媽媽吧  阮
Juan! Did you say something? Juan!
阮  就再說一次嘛
Juan, what did you say?
阮
Juan!
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
晚安啦  小寶貝
Good night, buddy.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey!
哇哦  這看起來很完美誒   嗯哼  你喜歡嗎
Wow, it's looking good. Huh? You like it?
看看那兒  我按照你意思把儲藏櫃按在了廚房島的盡頭
Check it out. I put the storage at the end of the island, like you suggested.
哇  這真的太棒了
Oh, hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
順便一提  那真是個好主意  太炫酷了吧
Great idea, by the way. It's awesome.
過來幫我們貼一些瓦吧  對啊
Why don't you come help us hang some tile? Yeah.
不了  我
No, I, uh...
那麼  這裡有
So, there's, um...
有些事情我想去做
There's something I'd like to do,
我想讓您們幫我準備一下
and I was hoping I could get your help setting it up.
沒問題  我們要準備些什麼  什麼都行
Sure. What are we setting up? Of course. Anything.
我剛跟凱倫和莎倫談過
So I was talking to Karen and Sharon, and they...
我媽媽幾個月前走了
Uh, my mom got out a few months ago, so...
我最近都沒見過她  我想和她見個面
And I haven't seen her. I was hoping I could see her.
可以  沒問題  當然可以
Yeah, sure. Yeah, of course.
肯定可以的啊  嗯嗯
Of course. I mean, that's... Yeah.
好的  謝謝您們
Cool. Thanks.
沒什麼  嗯  問題不大
Yeah. It's cool. Great.
太謝謝了
Okay. Thanks.
您們  額
You, uh...
那我就在外面等吧
I'll just wait outside. Okay.
媽
Mom!
嗨
Hi.
嗨  媽媽
Hi, Mom.
阮  麗塔
Juan, Lita.
嘿  阮  麗塔  快過來
Hey, Juan, Lita, come on!
快來快來
Come on.
怎麼回事了呢  我想和嘛嘛呆著
What's wrong? Come on. I want to stay with Mom.
你的媽媽在那裡啊
Your mommy's over there.
沒關系的  小寶貝  嗯嗯  沒關系的  親愛的
It's okay, sweetheart. It's okay, honey.
我們和你一起過去  我們就在這裡
We're gonna go with you. We're right here.
我們一起走吧  快來快來
We'll walk together. Come on.
慢點兒嘛
Slow down.
噢  我的孩子  你已經這麼大了啊
Oh, my babies, you got so big!
來給我抱抱
Come, mi amor.
嗨  我是休  我是卡拉的社工
Hi, I'm Sue. I'm Carla's caseworker.
你們肯定就是皮特和艾莉了  嗯嗯  我是Pete  嗨
You must be Pete and Ellie? Yeah, I'm Pete. Hi.
嗨  我是艾莉
Hey. I'm Ellie.
這是卡拉  她是  孩子們的親媽
This is Carla. She's... Their mom.
嗨  我是艾莉  非常高興見到你
Hi. I'm Ellie. Nice to meet you.
我是皮特
I'm Pete.
嘿  我想說謝謝你們幫忙照顧他們在
Hey, I wanted to say thank you for watching them while I was...
沒關系  他們都很乖
No problem. They've been doing great.
阮開始學習彈鋼琴了對吧  小家伙
Juan started playing piano. Right, buddy?
麗塔剛剛在拼寫測試拿了一百分
And Lita just got 100 on her last spelling test.
麗茲的足球隊打遍天下無敵手
And Lizzy's soccer team is undefeated.
好的  那麼你們四點鐘來接回我們吧
All right, so you guys gonna pick us up at 4:00?
沒問題  待會見
Okay. We'll see you in a bit.
嗯嗯  我們很快就回來  很快就回來
Yeah, we'll be back. We'll be back soon.
再見啦  小家伙們  很高興見到你
Bye, guys. Nice to meet you.
你還行嗎
You okay?
謝謝你們照顧他們  我們就像做了五個月保姆嗎
"Thanks for watching them"? Like we've just been fricking babysitting for five months?
她根本不像我以為的那樣
She's just not what I pictured at all.
她  她看起來很正常
She's... She kind of looks normal.
我感覺不太好  就像我們在破壞別人的家庭
I feel bad, like we're breaking up a family.
我們沒有搶走她的孩子  艾莉
We didn't take her kids, Ellie.
是法庭搶了  還有別忘了起因
The courts did. And don't forget why.
這些孩子之前生活得就像破屋裡的野貓
Those kids were living like feral cats in a crack house.
我知道  我知道  但她看起來還是很正常的
I know, I know, but she kind of... She looks okay.
我的意思是  莎倫說她已經四個月沒犯事了
I mean, Sharon said she's been clean for four months.
嗯  她沒犯事  那是因為她坐過牢了啊  艾莉
Yeah, she got clean because she was in jail, Ellie.
看看麗茲看著她親媽的眼神
Look at the way Lizzy's looking at her.
她親媽還是她親媽
She's still her mom.
我們沒有搶走她的孩子啊  艾莉
We didn't take her kids, Ellie.
那當時我就說  這位年輕女士
So I said, "Young lady,
如果我們再一次聽說你在咖啡廳裡亂扔食物
we hear about you throwing food in the cafeteria one more time,
你就會多次和我們兩個一起吃午餐
and you're gonna have a couple of lunch dates."
第二天  她還是亂扔食物
Next day, the behavior continued.
所以我們去了她的學校然後和她一起吃午飯
So we went to the school and joined her in the cafeteria.
和她所有的中學好朋友聊了天
Chattin' up all her middle school BFFs.
我跟他們講了一些我最好的的觀鳥故事
I walked them through some of my better bird-watching stories.
但他們完全不感興趣
They were completely uninterested.
不過她就沒有再亂扔食物了
But that food throwing has stopped!
妙啊  妙啊
Good. Good.
你願意分享一下你的故事嗎
Would you like to share your news?
關於沙發著火的故事嗎  不  關於你的二六聽訊
About the couch fire? No. About your .26 hearing.
二六聽訊  法庭決定孩子法定監護人的聽訊會
嗯嗯
Yes.
法庭已經依照法律
The court has legally cleared us...
把孩子判給我們了
to adopt.
把緹娜和瑞安判給我們了
To adopt Tina and Ryan!
太好啦  這真的太棒了
Yay! That is so great.
恭喜啊  我非常為你們感到高興
Congratulations, guys. I'm so happy for you.
這真是非常好的一個消息  我為你們感到高興
That is such great news. I'm so happy for both of you.
那麼下面有請皮特和艾莉
And next we have Pete and Ellie.
好吧  你們知道  我們的孩子已經
Well, you know, our kids have, what,
回去見了他們親媽四次了
had now four visits with their birth mom?
嗯哼  每一次他們都非常
Yeah. And every time they do,
非常興奮  特別在見了他們親媽後的那幾天
they're just crazy for a few days after.
天哪
Holy...
當他們平靜下來後  一切如常的時候
And just when things finally start to feel normal again,
他們就再去見他們親媽
they have another visit.
嗯嗯  我們感覺被排擠得很嚴重
Yeah, we just feel so rejected.
我也知道這可能讓你們覺得我很壞
And I know this probably makes me a really bad person,
但我真的一直希望他們親媽能回去坐牢
but I just keep wishing that their mom would go back to prison.
你才不是個壞人呢
You're not a bad person.
當有人對我們心愛的孩子做出可怕的事情是
When someone does terrible things to the children we love,
我們很難對那個人產生同情
it's not easy to find empathy for them.
但我們還是要盡量去試著同情
But we have to try, people.
無論發生什麼  孩子們陪伴你們的時間
Whatever happens, the time that your kids spent with you
已經對他們人生產生很大影響  嗯哼
made a big difference in their lives. Mm-hmm.
嗯  我知道  但我們就理應去
Yeah, I know, but then we're just supposed to...
等等  你剛剛說已經對他們產生影響  對的
Wait. Did you say "made" a difference? Yeah, she did.
我們之後再談
We-We'll talk after.
不 她說已經  這是過去式  這就是不同
No. She said "made." That's past tense. There's a difference.
我想知道這是什麼狀況  凱倫
I wanna know what's going on, Karen.
好吧
Well...
鑒於麗茲的親媽已經逐步開始與她的孩子們重歸於好
Since Lizzy's mom has been keeping up with her reunification steps,
法官把孩子判給你們的事可能懸了
the judge changed your .26 hearing to a Change of Circumstances hearing
法官將會決定孩子們是否跟回他們親媽生活
where he'll decide if the kids are ready to reunite.
棒
Nice.
太棒了
Really nice.
這簡直就是
No, this is...
你們剛還打算隱瞞著我們嗎
You weren't gonna share that with us?
我們一直在和這破事兒糾纏
We've been dealing with all of this shit!
我是說  他們亂發脾氣  弄得家裡一團糟  還有那可怕的態度
I mean, the tantrums, the messes, the attitude.
我甚至已經和麗塔玩了一百五十次糖果樂園
I have played 150 games of Candy Land with Lita.
糖果樂園  兒童類棋子游戲
你玩過糖果世界嗎
You ever play fricking Candy Land?
（標注：Candy Land一款適合幼兒的簡單賽車游戲）
太痛苦了  無聊透了
It's brutal! It's very dull.
我們試著和她多交流
We're making connections. Okay?
所以打算教麗塔學騎自行車
I mean I just taught Lita how to ride a bike.
阮和我在看《洛基 III》
Juan and I bonded over Rocky III.
（標注：Rocky III《洛奇III》由史泰龍拍攝並擔當主演的電影）
現在就連媽媽也要摻和進來了嗎
And now Mom's ready to reunite?
彼得  艾莉  我知道你們很失望
Pete, Ellie, I understand your frustration.
但要知道我們機構的首要目標就是
But we all need to keep in mind that until the kids are adopted,
讓孩子受到家庭的庇護
the primary goal of the system is family preservation.
那又有誰來保護我們的家庭呢  誰來呢
And what about preserving our family? Yeah.
事情還沒有蓋棺定論
Nothing has been decided yet.
那好  接下來  奧克托布
All right, October, that leaves you.
嗯 我也收養了一個大孩子
Well, I have gotten a placement.
他14歲了  還參加了少年籃球隊
Oh. He is 14 and does play JV basketball.
他身高有點低
But he is 5'2."
（標注：5'2'' 指最適合女性的身高）
皮膚很白染著紅頭發
And white, with red hair.
也沒什麼基礎
Absolutely no fundamentals whatsoever.
額  好吧  看起來我的問題有點不合時宜
Oh, I get it. My problems seem stupid now.
為什麼我總是最後一個呢
Why do I always have to go last?
停下來吧  -好的  我想說
Stop. Okay. I know. It's...
這很不專業
It's very unprofessional.
這簡直就是互助小組的反例
This is the opposite of a support group.
我會變成什麼樣子
What am I gonna look like?
你會看起來像個漂亮的公主哦  哇
You're gonna look like a beautiful princess. Oh!
那我像花朵一樣美麗嗎
Do I look like a flower?
嘿  嘿  嘿  伙計
Hey. Hey, hey, buddy.
-媽媽  嘿  孩子們  -哦  嗨  親愛的
Mom. Hey, kids. Oh! Hi, honey!
嘿  媽媽
Hey. Mom!
沒事的 沒事的  它們可以被洗掉的
No, no, no. It's totally washable.
可是  那是記號筆
It's, um... That's a Sharpie.
（標注:Sharpie記號筆的一種，用水很難洗掉）
額  是的  額  親愛的
Oh, yeah. Oh, dear.
親愛的  你能從櫃子上下來嗎  這很危險
Can you please get off the counter, honey? It's dangerous.
互助小組怎麼樣  太有趣了
How was care group? So much fun.
嘿  嘿  嘿  我們想告訴你們個消息
Hey, hey, hey. We have news.
-你懷孕了嗎  哦  天哪
You're pregnant? Oh, my God!
你為什麼這麼說  對不起  那是什麼消息呢
Why are you doing this to me? I'm sorry. No?
快把消息告訴他們吧
It's okay. No. Just tell them.
確定嗎
Yeah? Uh-huh.
馬上  馬上
Okay, okay.
我們也打算通過寄養所來領養孩子
We are going to adopt through foster care, just like you guys!
雖然我們不能懷孕
I mean, we did not get it at first,
但是我們遇到了你們  看到了收養孩子這種方式
and then we met yours and saw what a wonderful choice it was.
比做試管嬰兒要便宜的多了
Hell of a lot cheaper than in vitro too.
在這個決定中 你們對我們的影響挺大的
Which is not the reason, but it's a reason, if you're weighing factors.
所以我們打算下周開始上課啦
And we start classes next week!
你們覺得怎麼樣
What do you guys think?
我想  呃
I think, uh...
真是令人作嘔
I think I have to take a crap.
這好像不是我們期待中的反應
That's not the reaction we were looking for on that.
她一定是在嫉妒
She's jealous!
哦  嘿  哦  天哪  你在做什麼
Oh! Hey! Oh, my God! What are you doing?
怎麼了  請把這個還給我  Lizzy
What's going on? Please give this to me. Lizzy!
你不能拿走我的手機  她在做什麼
You're not allowed to take my phone! What's she doing?
天哪  她在浴室裡拍裸照
God! She's taking naked selfies in the bathroom!
她在拍自己的裸照嗎  別動我的手機 電話
She's taking naked selfies of herself? What are you doing to my phone?
我要刪除裡面的所有內容  全部刪除
I'm deleting everything here! Delete, delete, delete.
你到底拍了多少張  你到底為什麼這麼做
How many photos did you take? What is wrong with you?
大家都這麼做  沒什麼大不了的
Everyone does it! It's no big deal!
這很有問題  這很重要
It's a big, huge, giant deal!
15歲的女孩要自尊自愛
Fifteen-year-old girls should never be naked, ever!
你能拉著門嗎  不能看我的短信  把門打開
Can you take the door? Don't read my texts! Open the door!
如果你不馬上給我看照片  我可就沒什麼興趣了
"If you don't show me something soon, I might lose interest."
什麼  這個人是誰  麗茲  開門
What? Who is this person, Lizzy? Open the door!
哦  不  不  不  色情照  有張色情照
Oh, no. No, no. Dick pic! There's a dick pic!
來吧  孩子們  我們去客廳呆著
Come on, kids, we are going in the living room.
你是在和一個叫雅各布的人聊天嗎
Is this that kid Jacob you were talking about?
那個給你寄他性感照片的男孩兒嗎
That sweet kid from school is sending you photos of his beeswax?
天哪  這可是個老油條
Jesus, that is a trout!
（標注:Trout  指喜歡20歲年輕女孩子的40歲左右的男子）
離開這裡
Get out of here!
麗茲  現在快出來
Lizzy! Get out here now!
把電話還給我  放開
Give me the phone! Let go!
這並不時髦  麗茲  我再也不想聽你說話了
This is not cool Lizzy! I don't have to listen to you anymore,
你這個假媽媽
Pretend Mom!
不是...
This isn't...
你們還堅持這是一個好的選擇嗎
Still think it's a wonderful choice?
我們的孩子不會這麼做的
Our foster kids aren't gonna act like that.
只是你們的孩子而已
That's on you guys.
Dic pic是什麼
What exactly is a dick pic?
你覺得會是什麼呢  媽媽  色情照啊
What do you think it is, Mom? Wild guess. Dick. Pic.
親愛的  當我…面臨這種問題的時候
You know, honey, when I had... times like this,
我總是不斷思考
I had to search myself
並回憶
and remember...
一開始為什麼我選擇成為一名母親
why I became a mother in the first place.
這種思考很有幫助
And that was helpful.
這是雅各布家嗎  就是我們要去的地方嗎
Is this that kid Jacob's house? Is that where we're going?
冷靜點  好嗎  告訴我咱們在哪裡
Just calm down, okay? Please tell me where we are.
我可不想被逮捕
I don't want to get arrested.
你只需要相信我就行  下車吧
Will you just trust me? Come on.
哦  你好
Oh. Hi.
嘿  我不知道你們是否還記得我們
Hey. I don't know if you guys remember us.
寄養所見過的的彼得和艾莉
Pete and Ellie from foster orientation?
哦  記得  嗨  你好嗎
Oh, yeah. Hi. How you doing?
呃  我們能為你做些什麼呢
Uh, what can we do for you?
所以現在她想回來再一次成為一位母親
So now she wants to come back and be Mommy again.
而且看起來她真的有機會
And it looks like she's got a real shot.
麗茲  她對待我們就像對待敵人一樣
Lizzy, she's treating us like we're the enemy.
現在我們不知道該怎麼辦
Now we don't know what the hell to do.
所以我想知道為什麼你們的女兒如此優秀
So I just thought, I mean, your daughter turned out so great.
她在那裡學習嗎  嘿  布蘭達  你要下來嗎
Is she up there studying? Hey, Brenda, you gonna come down?
我們想和她談談
I thought maybe we could speak with her,
也許能讓我們像之前一樣抱有希望
and she'd get us pumped up like before.
有可能嗎  對的  那太好了  她太棒了
Is that a possibility? Yeah, that'd be great. She was amazing.
我們需要一次鼓舞人心的談話
We could use a pep talk right now.
嗯  布蘭達她  嗯…回到康復中心了
Um, Brenda is, um... back in rehab.
對不起  什麼  幾個月前我們發現她在吸毒
Excuse me, what? We caught her using a couple months ago.
你在跟我開玩笑嗎
Are you shitting me right now?
她那鼓舞人心  令人心曠神怡的演講
Her inspirational, heartwarming goddamn speech
是我們當初報名參加活動的主要原因
is the reason we signed up for this shit-show in the first place!
現在你告訴我她又變回了老樣子…噢
Now you're telling me she's back on... Ow!
你聽我說  瘋女人
You listen to me, crazy woman!
布蘭達一直在同毒品作鬥爭
Brenda has struggled with substance abuse
她11歲的時候被她母親的男朋友注射了冰毒
ever since her mother's boyfriend started her on meth when she was 11.
有時她會走入歧途  但她是個好孩子
Sometimes she stumbles. But she is a good kid.
她會認真干活  把自己整理的干干凈凈
And she's in there doing the work, getting herself clean.
你不知道會發生什麼
So you don't know what's gonna happen.
所以讓你感到沮喪  害怕  失落嗎
And this has you feeling what? Frustrated? Scared? Lost? Is that it?
對  我有點害怕  是的  沒錯這就是
Yes! I'm a little afraid to say anything, but yes, that's basically
我們的感受
how we feel.
這也正是你們孩子每天的生活感受
That's how your children feel every day of their lives.
當你領養他們的時候  你自我感覺良好
When you took this on, you felt good about yourself
因為你知道這很重要  對吧
because you knew that it mattered, right?
好吧  大家都知道的
Well, guess what.
重要的事情往往很困難
Things that matter are hard.
現在我知道布蘭達那
Now I know where Brenda
鼓舞人心的演講是從哪裡來的靈感了
gets her inspiring speech thing.
聽著  現在  你們就是孩子們的全部
Listen, guys, right now, you're all they've got.
所以你們的工作就是保證他們的安全
So your job is to keep them safe,
不論他們是否接受
whether they want you to or not.
他也被潛移默化的影響了
He's got it too.
太不可思議了  謝謝您
That was incredible. Thank you.
很抱歉我對你大發脾氣
I'm so sorry that I blew up at you.
還扇了你一巴掌
I'm sorry I slapped you!
沒事  這很好  嗯  十分抱歉
I know! That was crazy! I know. I apologize.
這很好  我需要它  我好久沒挨耳光了
It was good. I needed it. I haven't been slapped for a long time.
醍醐灌頂  茅塞頓開
It was a bit aggressive. It was a little bit out of line.
可以可以  親愛的
Well, you were, honey. You were.
好吧  親愛的  我們得走了
All right, honey, we gotta go.
我們得走了  保重
We gotta get going. Take care.
謝謝您
Thank you.
在Facebook上能找到你對吧  我會關注你的
You're on Facebook, right? I'll find you. Okay!
再見  再見  謝謝您
Bye! Bye! Thank you!
再見
Bye.
我們快進屋吧  快點
Let's get in the house right away, really quick.
好的  你到啦  再見  麗茲
Okay, you're all set. Bye, Lizzy.
過得愉快哦
Have a great day.
接下來  你把他們兩個送到學校
All right, look, you drop them off.
我會找到這個雅各布這小子  把事情搞清楚  好嗎
I'm gonna find this Jacob kid and get to the bottom of this, okay?
好的  好的
Okay. All right.
等等  彼得  就是他  什麼
Wait, Pete, that's him! What?
那個拿著湯罐子的紅頭發男生
Him? That redhead kid right there? The kid with the soup can for a...?
來吧  我要抓住他
Come on. I'm getting him.
你  猥瑣男  嘿  嘿
You! Dick pic! Hey! Hey!
嘿 有事嗎  伙計  想單挑嗎
Hey! Excuse me. What's up, man? Wanted to catch a fade, huh?
猥瑣男  裝無辜嗎
Dick pic! Think it's okay?
把你的小弟弟照片發給一個15歲的女孩
Sending pictures of your knob to a 15-year-old girl?
真幸運  我沒有馬上斃了你  小蘿蔔
You're lucky I don't end your life right now, carrot top.
我看到你寫給她的信：  如果你不來點什麼  我會
I saw what you wrote to her: "If you don't show me something, I'm
失去興趣的
gonna lose interest."
那是性侵犯  年輕人  真惡心
That's actually sexual assault, young man. It's disgusting!
你不是個大塊頭嗎  來來來  秀一下
Not such a big man now, are you? Come on, whip it out!
讓大家看看你為之驕傲的大家伙
Show everybody those big shaved plums you're so proud of!
我們要打電話給你媽媽  告訴校長
We're gonna call your mom, tell the principal, maybe even call the
還要報警
police.
你覺得怎麼樣  雅各布  我不是雅各布
What do you think of that, Jacob? My name's not Jacob!
什麼  我叫查理
What? My name is Charlie.
他是查理
That's Charlie.
我以為你確定他就是雅各布  錯了嗎
I thought you said his name was Jacob. Really?
我的小弟弟沒刮毛
And my plums aren't shaved.
他還不大
Or big.
我很抱歉  哦  天哪  我很抱歉  親愛的
I'm so sorry. Oh, God. I'm so sorry, honey.
來吧  伙計  深呼吸  這是個誤會
Come on, buddy, suck it up. It's a little snafu, okay?
來吧  給我一個擁抱  查理
Come on. Give me a hug, Charlie.
放松  看著我
All right, look at me.
你認識叫雅各布的人嗎
Do you happen to know anybody named Jacob
誰會和我們的女兒麗茲在一起
who might be hanging around with our daughter, Lizzy Viara?
看門人  成人用品店的看門人
The janitor? The adult-ass janitor?
-我的天  走  我們去找看門人
Oh, my God. Come on, let's get the janitor.
嘿  我很抱歉  艾莉  快點
Hey, I'm so sorry about this. Ellie, come on!
非常感謝  和他無關
Thank you so much! He didn't do any of that.
快點  艾莉 和他沒有一點關系
Come on, Ellie. He didn't do any of it!
快點  對不起  查理
Hurry up! I'm so sorry, Charlie!
我們上學要遲到了
I think we're gonna be late for school.
艾莉
Ellie
他在吃早飯  加油
He's on a Zamboni. Come on!
嘿  嘿  叫你呢
Hey! Hey, you!
嘿  我在和你說話呢
Excuse me. I'm talking to you.
你多大了  你想知道什麼
How old are you, Jump Street? Why you want to know?
-嘿  女士  把那個還我  那不是你的  他22歲了
Hey, lady, gimme that. That's not yours. He's 22!
他22歲  是的  我22歲了  那又怎麼樣
He's 22. Yeah, I'm 22. So what?
所以我們不是在虐待兒童  彼得
So this won't be child abuse. Pete!
嘿  你之前碰過  想過  聯系過我女兒  要是再有下次
Hey, you ever touch, text, or think about our daughter ever again,
那你就死定了
and you're a dead man.
我要起訴你  你們不是她的親生父母
I'm gonna sue you, man! You're not even her parents!
她親生父母難道不會這樣做嗎
Would not-her-parents do this?
佩佩小姐
Miss Peppers!
哇  哇  發生了什麼
Whoa. Whoa. What's happening here?
他一直給我們女兒發送淫穢評論和照片
This man has been sending lewd comments and photos to our daughter.
你今天要坐牢了  Jacob  你介意報警嗎
You're going to jail today, Jacob! You mind calling the police?
必須報警  佩佩小姐
Absolutely! Miss Peppers!
媽媽…
Mother...
謝謝  我們很感激
All right. We appreciate it.
伙計  我都沒碰過那個女孩
Man, I didn't even touch that girl.
滾蛋吧  混蛋  惡心的戀童癖
Bye-bye, scumbag. Filthy pedophile.
滾去享受性侵犯者的生活
Yeah. Enjoy your life as a sex offender.
惡心的戀童癖
Pedophile.
為什麼逮捕我們  那家伙把他的色情照
You're arresting us? The guy was sending pictures of his knob to a
發給了未成年
minor.
-你為什麼要逮捕我們  非常好  干得好
Why are you arresting us? Really good. Good work, guys.
必須要說  我聽說了你們的光輝事跡
For what it's worth, I heard what you guys did in there.
你們是好父母  照顧你的孩子
You're good parents, looking out for your kids.
如果又機會  我會做同樣的選擇…
If I'd had a chance to do the same...
孩子們  哦  天哪
The kids! Oh, my God!
阮  麗塔  哦  天哪  真對不起  孩子們
Juan, Lita! Oh, my God, I'm so sorry! Guys!
嘿  嘿  寶貝
Hey. Hey, baby.
天哪  真干凈
My God, it's so clean.
嗯  我的小“匪徒”們回來了
Well, there are my little gangsters.
保釋金交過了
Posting bail for my Petey.
我真的回到了過去的美好時光
Really took me back to the good old days.
謝謝  孩子們在哪裡
Thank you, by the way. Where are the kids?
凱倫不得不把他們帶到一個臨時的地方過夜
Karen had to take them to a temporary placement for the night.
她說這是她第一次聽說CPS在孩子聽證
She said it's the first time she's heard of CPS
的前一天晚上把他們從寄養家庭帶走
removing kids from their adoptive home the night before their hearing.
說到這兒  我看了你打印下來的陳述詞
Speaking of which, I found your statement to the judge on your printer.
需要進行一些修改
Needs some work.
媽媽  太晚了  我們上周已經提交了
Mom, it's too late. We submitted it last week.
盡管如此  還是要重新提交一份
Well, resubmit it! Jesus!
“我們要把最好的東西留給孩子
"We want whatever is best for the kids,
不管是和我們在一起還是回到親生母親身邊”
whether that means staying with us or returning to their birth mother. "
如果法官在利茲面前讀到這句話怎麼辦
What if the judge reads that crap in front of Lizzy?
媽媽  這正是我們寫下這句話的原因
That's why we wrote it like that, Mom.
如果因為陳述詞導致她媽媽沒有得到監護權
If she thinks our statement's the reason her mom doesn't get custody,
她會比現在更恨我們的
she's gonna hate us more than she does now.
她不恨你  她只會覺得你不愛她
She doesn't hate you. She just thinks you don't love her.
這份陳述詞將一無所用
And that statement ain't gonna help.
是麗茲和您說的嗎  哦  並不是  Ellie
Did Lizzy tell you that? Oh, come on, Ellie.
我的成長經歷和那個孩子很像
I grew up a lot like that kid.
如果你每天都被人罵你是屎
You get reminded what a sack of shit you are five times a day,
過了一會兒  你簡直不敢相信有人會愛你
after a while, you can't believe anyone could ever love you.
你知道的我們愛你  對吧
You know that we love you, right?
是的 我知道
No.
但不是你 我愛我自己
But that's not you, it's me.
我以為我已經可以看淡所有
I thought I just covered all that.
但我真的愛你們兩個
But I do love you both.
孩子們  睡一覺把
Get some sleep, kids.
在那之前別忘了改改陳述詞
After you fix that god-awful statement.
真的
Wow.
這裡既整潔又安靜
It's so clean and quiet in here.
我知道
I know.
但我討厭這樣
I hate it.
我也是
Me too.
-嘿  -嘿
Hey. Hey.
孩子們  我們很抱歉
Guys. We are so sorry.
我們很抱歉  你沒事吧
We are so sorry. Are you okay?
你知道嗎  我們坐著警車過來的
Guess what? We got a ride in a police car.
是嗎  有趣嗎
You did? Was that fun?
你們進監獄了嗎  是  我們…就在監獄裡
Did you guys go to prison? No. We were... just in jail.
阮  麗塔  過來吧
Juan. Lita. Come on.
媽媽在這裡  好的
Mom's here. Okay.
好的  各位  26號聽證會是關於維拉
Okay, folks, our .26 hearing is now a Change of Circumstance hearing
小姐的情勢變更
for a Miss Carla Viara.
-你是伊麗莎白 維拉小姐嗎  是的  法官大人
And you are Miss Viara, yes? She is, Your Honor.
今天和我們在一起的還有阮  麗塔和伊麗莎白
And also with us today are Juan, Lita, and Elizabeth Viara?
在這裡  在這裡
Here. Here!
你們兩個都拿到泰迪熊了嗎
And did you two each get a teddy bear?
是的  哦  它們很漂亮
Yes! Oh, those are good ones.
-你是伊麗莎白嗎  我是麗茲 先生
And you are Elizabeth? It's Lizzy, sir.
我是說  法官大人
I mean, Your Honor.
好的  麗茲  我知道你已經提交了一份聲明
And, Lizzy, I understand that you've submitted a statement.
寄養家庭父母萬戈爾夫婦也在場對嗎
And the foster parents, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner, are they present as well?
是的  法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
萬戈爾夫婦
And, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner,
當你因嚴重襲擊而被捕時  你們把阮和麗塔
is it accurate that you left Juan and Lita alone in your car
單獨留在了車裡  對嗎
while you were being arrested for aggravated assault?
-嗯  那…是的  法官大人  但我們是為了...
Well, that... Yes, Your Honor, but in our defense...
先生  我只關心Lizzy是不是撒謊
Sir, all I need to know is whether or not Lizzy is lying.
她當然沒撒謊
No, she's not lying.
在那次打擊之前
And prior to that assault,
你在校園裡和一個14歲的三好學生搭訕
did you accost a 14-year-old honor student in the same school yard
並鼓勵他掏出他光滑的蛋蛋嗎
and encourage him "to whip out his big, shaved plums"?
法官先生  我已經說過了  並且
I said that, Your Honor, but again,
我覺得是有人故意給她
I thought it was the person who sent her the...
Wagner夫人  你曾一度強迫Lizzy的所有朋友
Mrs. Wagner, did you at one time force Lizzy's friends to leave your
離開你家
home
從臥室窗裡爬出去離開嗎
by way of a bedroom window?
那是一扇落地窗  那還應該表揚你了
It was a ground floor window. Good. Points for you.
同時你還告訴Lizzy打電話叫CPS來
And at that same occasion, did you tell Lizzy to call CPS and to come
把他們都接走嗎
and take the kids?
你們誤會她了  我沒想那麼做
She didn't mean that. I did not mean that.
那次是在氣頭上
That was in the heat of an argument.
法官先生  我有份陳情書  我知道  看過了
Your Honor, I have a statement. Yes, I've read it, thank you.
我們重寫了一份  女士  那個  不用了吧
We actually wrote a new one. Ma'am, excuse me, but I have your...
拜托  法官大人  我們沒日沒夜的心血在這
Please, Your Honor, we were up late working on it. I can read it very
我讀的很快不耽誤時間
fast.
Lizzy曾問我為什麼收養他們
"Lizzy once asked us why we took them in.
我們當時無言以對
And at the time, we couldn't answer her."
女士  你還是請坐吧  法官先生 請允許我
Ma'am, please sit down. Please, Your Honor, can you let me say
您能允許我說出答案嗎
the answer?
不用了  請坐吧
No. Sit.
這場聽證會與你無關
This hearing is not about you.
從Lizzy的聲明來看  我們還會在這地方見面
Judging by Lizzy's statement, you might be back in court soon enough,
所以說這些話留給日後說吧
so let's save that heartwarming speech for that occasion.
Viara小姐
Okay. Now, Miss Viara,
看來你一直在跟進你的拜訪  那很好
I see that you've been keeping up with your visits. That's good.
我也明白你過去五個月一直很清醒
I also understand that you've been sober for the last five months.
現在還是如此嗎
Is that still the case?
是的  那可真是好消息了
Yes. That's very good news.
如果我讓你來照顧孩子們
And if I were to put the kids in your care,
您家裡住的下嗎
your current residence could accommodate them?
那沒問題
I think so.
麻雀雖小  五臟俱全的 法官先生
It's small, but it works... Your Honor.
Viara小姐  你覺得你能肩負起關心別人的重任嗎
And, Miss Viara, do you feel capable of responsibly caring
同時照顧Juan  Lita  Lizzy他們三個
for Juan, Lita, and Lizzy at this time?
Viara小姐
Miss Viara.
女士你在聽嗎
Mama.
當然  法官先生  沒問題
Yes, Your Honor. I'm capable now.
所有人準備吃晚餐啦
Everybody get ready for dinner.
給你
Here you go.
如果以後和我們媽媽一起住
What if when we go live with our mom,
她不知道怎麼弄我愛吃的面條花樣
she doesn't know how to make my noodles the way I like to have them?
伙計別擔心  Lizzy會給你做我們做過的芝士
Don't worry, pal. Lizzy will show her the way we do the cheese for you
這樣你媽媽不就會做了嗎
so your mom can make it for you just the way you like.
對哦  別擔心啦
Yeah. Okay.
我們一起的最後一晚啦  大家別垂頭喪氣的
Come on, guys. Don't be sad on our last night.
我覺得我們應該感謝Pete和Ellie
You know what? I think we should tell Pete and Ellie thank you,
他們真的為我們付出很多 不是嗎
you know, for everything they've done for us, yeah?
謝謝你  我也要感謝你 小家伙
Thank you. Well, thank you, pal.
謝謝大家
Yeah, thank you, guys.
Lita你呢  我不想說話
Lita? I don't want to say anything.
怎麼了寶貝
Oh, honey.
我去瞅一眼Lita
I'm just gonna go check on Lita.
我意思是  除非你想
I mean, unless you want to.
對  其實我想說謝謝
Yeah, I would, actually. Thanks.
怎麼了小家伙 你一勺都沒動
Come on, buddy. You haven't touched your pasta.
要不我給你在熱熱吧
You want me to reheat it for you?
沒關系啦小家伙
It's okay, buddy.
不要難過  小家伙
That's okay, buddy.
好夢  小家伙  晚安啦
Good night, buddy. Good night.
晚安寶貝  我愛你
Sweetie, good night. I love you.
我也愛你
Love you too.
你所有的球場熊都在這裡啦  包括那些新的
Okay, all your court bears are in here, the new ones as well.
說到這兒了
Speaking of court, um,
很抱歉  我寫給法官的那些話
I just wanted to apologize for what I wrote to the judge.
事實如此
It was all true.
可能有點脫題  但是別往心裡去
It was a little out of context maybe, but there's no hard feelings.
其實我也剛好想給你我們寫的那份聲明
Actually, I wanted to give you the statement we wrote
就是法庭上沒機會讀的那封 你看吧
that we couldn't read in court, just so you have it.
對
Yeah.
小家伙們  媽媽來啦
Guys, Mom's here.
收拾東西 準備出發
All right. Get up! Come on. Let's go.
Lita  快去收拾你的東西
Lita, come on, get your stuff.
再見咯  肉球
Bye, Meatball.
嗨  我給Lita多帶了個車座  怕你們這兒沒
Hey. I've got a car seat for Lita if you don't have one.
怎麼是你們來接我們  媽媽呢
You guys picking us up? Where's Mom?
她應該今早和我們在辦公室碰面的
She was supposed to meet us at the office this morning
但她放鴿子了
and she didn't show.
我的天
Oh, no.
她電話也不接
She didn't answer her phone.
你們去她家看了嗎  萬一她出事了呢
Did you go to her house? What if something happened to her?
我們當然去看了  她很羞愧
Yes, we went to see her. She was very ashamed.
她說  她還是做不到
She said... she can't do it.
我不相信  如果她不想  為什麼要填那麼多表
No, she didn't. Because why would she, um, fill out all the forms
費那麼多事找法庭人員尋親人員
and the court stuff and reunification stuff if she didn't...
Lizzy  你媽媽說你填完了所有表  我幫忙了
Lizzy, your mom said you filled out all those forms. I helped,
還有呢
but so what?
她感覺她在被逼著接受
She felt she was being pushed into something that she wasn't ready
她沒準備好的事
for.
並不是  沒有人逼她  她已經準備好了
No. I didn't push her. She's ready!
讓我來勸說吧
Just let me talk to her, please,
效果或許會好一點
and then we can figure something out.
寶貝  她本來能帶我回家的
Honey. And she can take me home.
親愛的  我們看到她第一眼就明白了
Honey, when we saw her, it was obvious.
她又重蹈覆轍了
She's using again.
她不會來了  寶貝
She's not coming, baby.
很抱歉  寶貝
Sweetie, we're so sorry.
Lizzy
Lizzy.
我去找她  你留下看好孩子們
I'll go get her. You watch the kids.
在這裡等我 好不好  Lizzy
Just wait there, okay? Lizzy!
Lizzy
Lizzy!
Lizzy  Lizzy
Lizzy? Lizzy!
Lizzy  請不要管我了  你們又不是我親生父母
Lizzy. Please just go away. You're not my parents.
是  你說得對  但我們永遠陪伴你
No, we're not. But you know what we are? We're here.
我們一直在你身邊  用心去愛你
That's right, we're here and we love you.
怎麼可能  你們真的懂我嗎
What? No, you don't. You don't even know me.
這邊怎麼了
Hey, what the hell's going on out here?
您能讓我們單獨呆會兒嗎
Could you just give us a few minutes, please?
沒問題  不好意思啊
Oh, okay. Sorry.
Lizzy  親愛的  我們當然懂你
Lizzy, honey, we do know you.
比如你討厭芝士
We... We know that you hate cheese,
但你又超喜歡芝士漢堡
but you really love cheeseburgers.
我們還知道  早上你要是心情好了
And we know that when you feel good in the morning,
你會化的妝會比心情不好時淡一點點
you put on a little less makeup than you do on the bad days.
沒錯吧  而且我們知道  對你來說
Exactly. And we know that the most important thing in the world to you
世上最重要的事是保護好Juan和Lita
is to protect Juan and Lita from the things nobody protected you from.
我們說的對嗎  是不是 寶貝
We know that about you, right? Yes, honey.
你們做的很棒了
You guys are doing good.
-對不起  -我們知道還有很多我們不了解的事
I'm sorry. We know there's so much we don't know.
但如果你害怕我們對壞消息
But if you're afraid we can't handle knowing the bad stuff, or the
或可怕的事物處理不好
scary stuff,
我們會做得很好  我保證
we can, I promise.
對  帶著這個承諾  不管發生什麼 一起面對
Yeah, bring it. Whatever you got, we want it.
因為我們愛你  Lizzy
Because we love you, Lizzy.
求你們別說了  走吧
Stop saying that. Please just go away, please.
走吧
Please.
Lizzy還好嗎  小家伙  她現在有點喪氣
Is Lizzy okay? She's a little upset right now, buddy.
那你還好嗎  我沒事
Are you okay? Yeah, I'm good.
看看誰來了
Here she is.
所以…
So...
我還是覺得這兒最好
um, here's what I think is best.
當你陷入這件事的時候
I know Juan and Lita are more like what you had in mind when you got
你的腦子裡只有Juan和Lita
into this.
過來 寶貝
Come on, baby.
我覺得最好還是你收養他們
So I think the best thing is for you to adopt them.
還有  我會讓Karen給我重新找個地方
And... And I'll just ask Karen for, um, a different placement.
所以  別這樣
So... No.
沒事兒  這樣最好  不  一點都不好
No, it'll be good. No, honey.
我們還需要你帶Juan和Lita呢
We need your help with Juan and Lita.
沒有你我們可做不到
We're not doing this without you.
需要幫忙了隨時聯系我 我會常來
I'll visit all the time and you can call me if you need help for
在家看看
anything.
不可能  Pete  我現在真不想為這個吵
No. Pete, I really don't want to argue about this right now.
我不管  我說過那不可能  明白嗎
I don't care. I said no. That's not happening, okay?
你和我們在一起  對
You're with us now. Yeah.
你明白嗎  我們覺得冥冥之中自有天意
And you know why? We've got a cosmic connection.
對  我們覺得冥冥之中自有天意
That's right, we've got a cosmic connection.
我知道你們現在可憐我  你們不用這樣
I know you feel sorry for me right now, but you really don't have to..
和剛發生的一切都無關
It's got nothing to do with what just happened.
Ellie給你的法庭陳述呢
Where's the court statement Ellie gave you?
看到沒  大聲讀
See this? Read that.
Lizzy曾問我為什麼我們收養他們
"Lizzy once asked me why we did this, why we took them in.
那時我給不了她答案
We couldn't give her an answer at the time.
這麼做是因為我們感覺生命中錯過了什麼
We did it because something was missing in our lives, but we didn't
我們又渾然不知
know what it was.
原來就是你們
It was Juan, Lita, and Lizzy."
明白了嗎
You see?
你就是我們缺少的那一塊
You were what was missing, Lizzy.
現在既然我們在一起了
But now you're here and you are stuck with us.
對啊  我們要出現在每個球場游戲中
That's right. We're gonna be at every soccer game.
我們會對你的成績火冒三丈
We're gonna be all over your ass about your grades.
我們要給你買人生第一件舞會禮服
We're gonna buy you your first prom dress.
一定會超好看的  既可愛又不會暴露太多
It's gonna be really pretty. But not too revealing. Super sweet.
就那種不會很性感的
You know, not too sexy.
就像  你會是最甜美的那個
Just like... really, that gorgeous sweet spot.
對哦  當你高中畢業了
Yeah. And when you graduate high school,
我們會在前排講你的糗事
we're gonna be in the front row embarrassing you.
當你大學畢業的時候  我們還那麼干
We're gonna be in the front row again when you graduate college, or
或者不上都成
even if you don't.
你一定會大學畢業  你那麼聰明
You will be graduating college, 'cause it's so important and you're
對你來說很重要
so smart.
我不會逼你  但是大學畢業機遇更多
I don't mean to push, but it just opens up so many more opportunities.
但不論如何  我們都會伴你左右
But either way, we're gonna be there for you.
直到某天  我會在你的婚禮上送別你
And someday I'm gonna give you away at your wedding.
即使我認為他是個笨蛋  他也不配
Even if I think the guy's a pissant and he's not good enough for my
我家小姑娘
little girl.
多好啊  將來某天
That's right. Someday in the future.
遙遠而觸不可及的未來
Someday in the way, way, way off, deep, deep, deep distant future.
lizzy  我們回家吧
Lizzy, can we go home now?
我也這樣想的
Yeah, I guess we can.
我知道你不喜歡這樣
I know you don't like this,
但你偶爾也要習慣一下  好不好
but you're gonna have to get used to it once in a while, okay?
我能來一個嘛  自從我認識你
Can I get one? I haven't gotten a single hug from you since I've
我一個都沒抱過
known you.
給個面子吧
Please?
嗨  我雖然不明白發生什麼了
Hi. I don't know the whole context of everything.
但我只想知道我能不能也抱一下下
But I'm just wondering if I can just get in on that hug a little bit.
不用不用  心領了  謝謝您
We're good! Thank you so much. We're good, thank you.
對不起  我不應該這樣的  你們繼續
Sorry. That was just wrong. Yeah, I just do that. You guys hug.
我有點暈頭了
I crossed a boundary there.
一切也都會好起來的
Everything's gonna work out great too.
我敢保證
I can tell.
嗨
Hi!
喔  太感謝了
Oh! Oh, thank you!
再見咯  回見
Bye. Bye!
你們一起嗎  你們認識他們嗎
Are you with them? Do you know those guys?
認識啊  怎麼了
Yeah. Why?
你們想進來坐坐嗎
Do you guys want to come in?
我  我做了熱乎的派
Uh... I-I made a pie.
不用了  謝謝  必須去了
No, thank you. Yes!
Karen  那可是派啊  你還不了解我嗎
Karen! It's pie. You know I love pie.
太好了 真的 我想法太多了現在
Great. Yeah, I just... I have so many feelings.
上個廁所  穿上鞋  我們出發了  好嗎
Go potty, put your shoes on. We're gonna go, okay?
好噠
Okay!
Juan  哥們  你干嘛呢
Whoa, Juan. What are you doing, buddy?
可不能穿運動鞋  今天我們得看起來酷
You can't wear sneakers. We gotta look good today.
老媽你見我手機了嗎
Mom, have you seen my phone?
沒啊 你意思是你手上那個是吧
Uh, no. Wait, you mean the one in your hand?
Lita  小寶貝  你上過廁所了嗎
Lita, honey, did you go potty?
我去過啦  非常棒
I went potty! Okay, good job.
全部上個廁所去  我去過啦
Everybody go potty! Yeah, I went potty.
帶上我們要帶的包裹了嗎  -是的  都準備好了
Got that packet we're supposed to bring? Yeah, I'm all set.
出發咯  出發
Let's go, guys. Let's go.
我要贏咯
I'm gonna beat you!
當然不行
No, no, no.
專心開車  行吧
No distracted driving, okay?
沒問題  確定嗎
All right. All right?
她來開車  真的呀
She's gonna drive. Oh, yeah?
是的  我拿著手機坐前排
Yes, but I have the phone and I'll sit in the front
以防我不得不抓方向盤或者停車  好嗎
in case I have to grab the wheel or shut down the power, okay?
Sandy  快點快點  要開始啦
Sandy, come on, it's started!
我沒遲到吧  剛剛好
Did I make it? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
那是啥啊
What's that?
Lizzy給我做的  你沒有嗎
Lizzy made it for me. You didn't get one?
你居然得到了一個短袖
You got a T-shirt? You got a T-shirt?
請諸位就座
You may all be seated.
大家早上好
Good morning, folks.
眾所周知  家庭法庭很重要…
You know, family court is important...
稍等一下  等等  等等
Wait. Wait! Wait! Wait.
Sandy奶奶就座完畢  可以開始啦
Grandma Sandy's in the house. We can begin.
我說的沒錯吧  別鬧
Told you we'd make it. Stop it!
-這些座被占了  對啊  就是給我占的
These seats are saved. Yeah, they're saved for me.
往過挪  別鬧啦
Move over. Stop it!
法官先生您繼續  感謝配合  洛尼特奶奶
Go ahead, Judge. Thank you, Grandma Sandy.
居然送她短袖
She got a T-shirt.
眾所周知 家庭法庭意義重大
You know, family court is important work.
但是做好也不容易
But it's difficult work.
我們日復一日地處理一些事情
We spend day in and day out dealing with things
處理我們覺得大家不該面對的事情
that we feel no family should have to go through.
所以在這難得的幾天裡  當我們笑起來時
So on these rare days when we get to smile at work,
意味著這些任務圓滿完成
these days mean a great deal to all of us.
我或許看不到  但我很多愁善感
And I may not look it, but I'm a huge cornball
我以此而活
and I live for this.
Ronit
Ronit?
我懂
Yeah!
我超愛這歌
I love this song.
今天大家共聚一起來組建新家庭
We are here today to officially create a new family.
Elinore  Wagner和Peter
Peter and Elinore Wagner,
今天你們決定好要和Juan Lita Lizzy成為一家人了嗎
do you wish to adopt Juan, Lita, and Lizzy into your family today?
毫無疑問 法官先生
Yes, Your Honor. Yes, Your Honor.
這歌聽的我多愁善感的
It's just the song that's got me a little emotional.
Juan  Lita  和Lizzy
Juan, Lita, and Lizzy,
你們願意做Elinore  Wagner和Peter的孩子嗎
would you like Peter and Elinore to be your mom and dad?
我願意
Sure.
毫無疑問  那必須的呀
Yes, please. Yes!
鑒於此
Well, then,
按照法規以及加州賦予我的權力
by the authority vested in me by the state of California,
我宣布你們正式成為一家人
I pronounce you a family.
給您  太感謝了
Here you go. Thank you.
要和法官合個影嗎  那當然了
Would you like to take a picture with the judge? Yeah, sure.
謝謝
Thank you.
來吧
Yeah, let's do it.
馬上該我們啦
That's gonna be us soon.
還有我呢  我也是這家的啊
Oh, I'm part of this family too.
哈哈 感謝您  還有我呢
Okay, thank you. Wait, me too!
我也想過去拍 你確定嗎  我們還沒
I'd like to be in the picture. Are you sure? We're not...
我們一起去  他們一定也願意
We should all go. I think they'd like that.
那就走
Okay. Okay. Yeah.
各就位啦
Okay! Okay.
都到齊了嗎
Anybody else?
還有你呢  快一起來
Yeah, you too. Come on!
這下圓滿啦
Okay, I think that's everybody.
喊 全家福  全家福
Say "Family." Family!